<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!-- CLASSIC -->
    <string name="classic_blt_sandwich_desc">A near-perfect balance of sweet, smoky, crusty, and salty, the BLT is what food dreams are made of. If only it were healthy to eat bacon and mayo on a daily basis</string>
    <string name="best_grilled_cheese_sandwich_desc">It\'s the first meal that most of us learn how to cook at home by ourselves. It\'s salty, gooey, crisp, buttery, and comforting in all the right ways</string>
    <string name="roasted_vegetable_sandwich_desc">This wonderful Italian style sandwich is finished off with a drizzling of vinaigrette. Pile it high!</string>
    <string name="cuban_sandwich_desc">Despite being so simple, the Cuban sandwich is packed full of flavour and all of the flavours work so well together!</string>

    <!--Luxe-->
    <string name="steak_foie_gras_desc">Creamy, controversial foie gras comes together with freezer-aisle steak in this cheesy sandwich</string>
    <string name="crab_sandwich_desc">This delicious crab sandwich recipe is great for any outdoor party, day or night</string>
    <string name="caviar_quail_eggs_desc">When adding rich ingredients like creme fraiche and caviar, the smaller size also feels less over-indulgent</string>
    <string name="lobster_roll_desc">Innovators prefer a crunchy, tangy and slightly spicy version of the lobster salad that includes celery, lettuce, lemon juice and a pinch of cayenne. Purists don't</string>
    <string name="porteno_lomito_desc">Each of these mighty sandwiches can be 10 cm tall, filled with about 250gms of hand-shaved pork loin, avocado, celery and plenty of mayonnaise</string>
    <string name="bacon_nan_roll_desc">Invented by Dishoom in England with a perfect anglo-indian style and a proper addition of spicy chutney, cream cheese and coriander</string>
    <string name="open_sausage_desc">A trimmed down version of a Italian sandwich classic. It is as healthy as it is tasty</string>
    <string name="croque_monsieur_desc">The name is based on the verb croquer ("to bite") and the word monsieur ("mister"). It first made appearance in 1910, Paris</string>
    <string name="croque_madame_desc">A croque monsieur served with a poached or lightly fried egg on top is known as a croque madame</string>
    <string name="club_sandwich_desc">Dated as far back as 1899 it's a sandwich of occasionally toasted bread, sliced cooked poultry, fried bacon, lettuce, tomato and mayonnaise</string>
    <string name="pastrami_on_rye_desc">Pastrami a meat product usually made from beef, and sometimes from pork, mutton or turkey</string>
    <string name="veal_schnitzel_desc">A schnitzel is meat, thinned by pounding with a meat tenderizer, coated with flour, beaten eggs and bread crumbs, and then fried.</string>
    <string name="muffaletta_desc">The muffuletta is the quintessential New Orleans sandwich of cured meats, cheese and tangy olive salad piled onto a sturdy Italian loaf</string>
    <string name="smoked_eel_desc">With a hunk of crisp, golden sourdough holding everything together, the oily sweetness of smoked eel with fiery horseradish cream and Dijon mustard.</string>
    <string name="reuben_sandwich_desc">The Reuben sandwich is an hot sandwich composed of corned beef, Swiss cheese, sauerkraut and Thousand Island dressing, grilled between slices of rye bread</string>
    <string name="clam_roll_desc">A properly fried clam is beautifully bronzed with a light, crisp coating, and it bursts with briny, oceanic flavor when you bite in</string>
    <string name="hoisin_glazed_salmon_desc">Quick-pickled cukes give these burgers tart crunch. Panko and egg white hold the patties together. Use cilantro leaves on the burgers as you would lettuce for herby freshness.</string>
    <string name="pan_bagnat_desc">The name of the sandwich comes from the local Provençal language, Nissart, in which pan banhat and the alternative spelling pan bagnat mean "bathed bread"</string>

    <!-- SPICE -->
    <string name="vietnamese_desc">This sandwich is the best for those who would like to add some spice to their life with some jalapeno, garlic and spice powder</string>
    <string name="spicy_chic_fillet_desc">Created by Todd Wilbur in his book "Even More Top Secret Recipes". To make this a little healthier, just broil the sandwiches in the oven</string>
    <string name="spicy_egg_salad_desc">For anyone who loves egg mayo and love spices, this is really a win - win recipe. Tastes better when prepared with toasted wholegrain English muffins</string>
    <string name="roast_beef_avocado_desc">This sandwich is to die for! If you like the ingredients, you'll love them together in this sandwich!. Don't believe? Try it out now.</string>
    <string name="mint_chutney_desc">This veg sandwich is from bombay aka Mumbai. Found anywhere in Mumbai, it is ideal for picnics, school lunch, evening snacks or short eats.</string>
    <string name="torta_ahogada_desc">The torta ahogada was created accidentally when a torta was dropped into the salsa container. A delicious accident indeed.</string>
    <string name="austrian_bosna_desc">Bosna is both the name for the sandwich and the sausage in the sandwich. The sausage was originally called Nadanitza</string>
    <string name="deviled_ham_desc">Deviled ham is ground ham with added spices such as hot sauce, cayenne pepper, hot peppers, or mustard. This process is called deviling or spicing up.</string>
    <string name="pulled_pork_desc">Pulled Pork - Pork cooked slowly over a low heat until it is tender enough to be pulled into strips, often prepared with a barbecue sauce</string>
    <string name="banh_mi_desc">The word is derived from bánh (bread) and mì (wheat bread), or more specifically the baguette, was introduced by the French during its colonial period.</string>
    <string name="the_dagwood_desc"> It was named after Dagwood Bumstead, a central character in the comic strip Blondie, who is frequently illustrated making enormous sandwiches</string>
    <string name="katsu_sando_desc">Tonkatsu, like many things Japanese, runs from low-end comfort food to high-end perfection. You can make it at home or have white gloved waiters bring it to you.</string>
    <string name="chicken_shawarma_desc">Shawarma is a Middle Eastern dish of garlicky meat or poultry served on pitas. This chicken version is flavored with a savory yogurt sauce.</string>
    <string name="roti_john_desc">Roti is a Hindi, Urdu and Malay for bread, more generally for any bread-based food I have no idea who John is but this is a delicious breakfast or snack.</string>
    <string name="ham_cheese_desc">Sliced bread, cheese and cooked ham are very readily available in Western supermarkets and as a result ham and cheese sandwiches are quick and easy to prepare.</string>
    <string name="oyster_roll_desc">Hot pepper sauce is the traditional condiment, but we've improvised a little, using chipotle mayonnaise to add a layer of smokiness instead of pure heat.</string>

    <!-- GUILTY -->
    <string name="simple_tuna_melt_desc">Eating a late-night tuna melt in front of a woman is a sure sign you have completely stopped giving a crap. The taste speaks for itself</string>
</resources>