<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!-- CLASSIC -->
    <string name="classic_blt_sandwich_desc">A near-perfect balance of sweet, smoky, crusty, and salty, the BLT is what food dreams are made of. If only it were healthy to eat bacon and mayo on a daily basis</string>
    <string name="best_grilled_cheese_sandwich_desc">It\'s the first meal that most of us learn how to cook at home by ourselves. It\'s salty, gooey, crisp, buttery, and comforting in all the right ways</string>
    <string name="roasted_vegetable_sandwich_desc">This wonderful Italian style sandwich is finished off with a drizzling of vinaigrette. Pile it high!</string>
    <string name="cuban_sandwich_desc">Despite being so simple, the Cuban sandwich is packed full of flavour and all of the flavours work so well together!</string>
    <string name="bombay_vada_pav_desc">A simple creation involving a deep fried potato patty with some coriander and spices. It originated as a street food in Mumbai</string>
    <string name="cheese_steak_desc">Cheesesteak was developed in the early 20th century "by combining frizzled beef, onions, and cheese in a small loaf of bread".</string>
    <string name="shripm_po_desc">In this shrimp po boy recipe, the paper-thin crust and pillowy crumb of a New Orleans–style French roll is essential as is Crystal hot sauce.</string>
    <string name="italian_hero_desc">It comes with a combination of mortadella, capicola, and Genoa salami. At a good Italian delicatessen, you'll be able to find the peppers and sliced meats</string>
    <string name="meatball_sub_desc">The art of the meatball sandwich is all about the construction&#8230; well, and the meatballs, of course. You can eat them as is</string>
    <string name="patty_melt_desc">In case you don’t know the strict definition, a patty melt is a beautiful, luscious, delicious cross between a grilled cheese and a hamburger</string>
    <string name="fish_fillet_desc">Skip the fast-food fish sandwiches and make them at home. They're 15-minutes fast and they are much more healthier</string>
    <string name="kentuky_hot_desc">It was one of two signature sandwiches created by chefs at the Brown Hotel shortly after its founding in 1923</string>
    <string name="the_elvis_desc">Also known as Peanut butter, banana and bacon sandwich is very tasty, especially on cold winter days!</string>
    <string name="fried_bologna_desc">The bologna sandwich, fried or unfried, has been elevated to a regional specialty in the Midwest, Appalachia, and the South</string>
    <string name="open_chicken_desc">This flavorful sandwich will add brightness to even the coldest winter day. Serve it with fresh seasonal citrus or other fruit</string>
    <string name="chicken_waffle_desc">Breakfast meets dinner in this play on the Southern favorite. The sauce is full of flavor that blends nicely</string>
    <string name="jambon_beurre_desc">Sold all over Paris, from boulangeries to street vendors I thought less of it. But once I tasted it, I became obsessed</string>
    <string name="creamed_eggs_desc">The dish is often used as a way to use up leftovers, common additions include chopped ham, veal, chicken, lobster, peas, etc.</string>
    <string name="chicken_parmesan_desc">But when life gives you massive amounts of excess chicken Parm, then there's only one thing to do: Make Chicken Parm sandwiches</string>

    <!--===================Luxe=========================-->
    <string name="steak_foie_gras_desc">Creamy, controversial foie gras comes together with freezer-aisle steak in this cheesy sandwich</string>
    <string name="crab_sandwich_desc">This delicious crab sandwich recipe is great for any outdoor party, day or night</string>
    <string name="caviar_quail_eggs_desc">When adding rich ingredients like creme fraiche and caviar, the smaller size also feels less over-indulgent</string>
    <string name="lobster_roll_desc">Innovators prefer a crunchy, tangy and slightly spicy version of the lobster salad that includes celery, lettuce, lemon juice and a pinch of cayenne. Purists don\'t</string>
    <string name="porteno_lomito_desc">Each of these mighty sandwiches can be 10 cm tall, filled with about 250gms of hand-shaved pork loin, avocado, celery and plenty of mayonnaise</string>
    <string name="bacon_nan_roll_desc">Invented by Dishoom in England with a perfect anglo-indian style and a proper addition of spicy chutney, cream cheese and coriander</string>
    <string name="open_sausage_desc">A trimmed down version of a Italian sandwich classic. It is as healthy as it is tasty</string>
    <string name="croque_monsieur_desc">The name is based on the verb croquer ("to bite") and the word monsieur ("mister"). It first made appearance in 1910, Paris</string>
    <string name="croque_madame_desc">A croque monsieur served with a poached or lightly fried egg on top is known as a croque madame</string>
    <string name="club_sandwich_desc">Dated as far back as 1899 it\'s a sandwich of occasionally toasted bread, sliced cooked poultry, fried bacon, lettuce, tomato and mayonnaise</string>
    <string name="pastrami_on_rye_desc">Pastrami a meat product usually made from beef, and sometimes from pork, mutton or turkey</string>
    <string name="veal_schnitzel_desc">A schnitzel is meat, thinned by pounding with a meat tenderizer, coated with flour, beaten eggs and bread crumbs, and then fried.</string>
    <string name="muffaletta_desc">The muffuletta is the quintessential New Orleans sandwich of cured meats, cheese and tangy olive salad piled onto a sturdy Italian loaf</string>
    <string name="smoked_eel_desc">With a hunk of crisp, golden sourdough holding everything together, the oily sweetness of smoked eel with fiery horseradish cream and Dijon mustard.</string>
    <string name="reuben_sandwich_desc">The Reuben sandwich is an hot sandwich composed of corned beef, Swiss cheese, sauerkraut and Thousand Island dressing, grilled between slices of rye bread</string>
    <string name="clam_roll_desc">A properly fried clam is beautifully bronzed with a light, crisp coating, and it bursts with briny, oceanic flavor when you bite in</string>
    <string name="hoisin_glazed_salmon_desc">Quick-pickled cukes give these burgers tart crunch. Panko and egg white hold the patties together. Use cilantro leaves on the burgers as you would lettuce for herby freshness.</string>
    <string name="pan_bagnat_desc">The name of the sandwich comes from the local Provençal language, Nissart, in which pan banhat and the alternative spelling pan bagnat mean "bathed bread"</string>

    <!-- SPICE -->
    <string name="vietnamese_desc">This sandwich is the best for those who would like to add some spice to their life with some jalapeno, garlic and spice powder</string>
    <string name="spicy_chic_fillet_desc">Created by Todd Wilbur in his book "Even More Top Secret Recipes". To make this a little healthier, just broil the sandwiches in the oven</string>
    <string name="spicy_egg_salad_desc">For anyone who loves egg mayo and love spices, this is really a win - win recipe. Tastes better when prepared with toasted wholegrain English muffins</string>
    <string name="roast_beef_avocado_desc">This sandwich is to die for! If you like the ingredients, you\'ll love them together in this sandwich!. Don\'t believe? Try it out now</string>
    <string name="mint_chutney_desc">This veg sandwich is from bombay aka Mumbai. Found anywhere in Mumbai, it is ideal for picnics, school lunch, evening snacks or short eats</string>
    <string name="torta_ahogada_desc">The torta ahogada was created accidentally when a torta was dropped into the salsa container. A delicious accident indeed</string>
    <string name="austrian_bosna_desc">Bosna is both the name for the sandwich and the sausage in the sandwich. The sausage was originally called Nadanitza</string>
    <string name="deviled_ham_desc">Deviled ham is ground ham with added spices such as hot sauce, cayenne pepper, hot peppers, or mustard. This process is called deviling or spicing up</string>
    <string name="pulled_pork_desc">Pulled Pork - Pork cooked slowly over a low heat until it is tender enough to be pulled into strips, often prepared with a barbecue sauce</string>
    <string name="banh_mi_desc">The word is derived from bánh (bread) and mì (wheat bread), or more specifically the baguette, was introduced by the French during its colonial period</string>
    <string name="the_dagwood_desc"> It was named after Dagwood Bumstead, a central character in the comic strip Blondie, who is frequently illustrated making enormous sandwiches</string>
    <string name="katsu_sando_desc">Tonkatsu, like many things Japanese, runs from low-end comfort food to high-end perfection. You can make it at home or have white gloved waiters bring it to you</string>
    <string name="chicken_shawarma_desc">Shawarma is a Middle Eastern dish of garlicky meat or poultry served on pitas. This chicken version is flavored with a savory yogurt sauce</string>
    <string name="roti_john_desc">Roti is a Hindi, Urdu and Malay for bread, more generally for any bread-based food I have no idea who John is but this is a delicious breakfast or snack</string>
    <string name="ham_cheese_desc">Sliced bread, cheese and cooked ham are very readily available in Western supermarkets and as a result ham and cheese sandwiches are quick and easy to prepare</string>
    <string name="oyster_roll_desc">Hot pepper sauce is the traditional condiment, but we\'ve improvised a little, using chipotle mayonnaise to add a layer of smokiness instead of pure heat</string>

    <!-- SWEET -->

    <string name="cara_choco_ban_desc">This fun, gooey treat makes a great after-school snack. The marshmallows are slightly charred and the bread is cleverly caramelized for double the toasty flavor</string>
    <string name="choco_oat_moon_desc">The cookies are oatmeal cookies with chunks of dried cherries, dark chocolate, and pecans. As you can see, this dessert is quite a mouthful</string>
    <string name="blue_choco_panini_desc">These are best served immediately, so if you\'re planning for dessert, just assemble them in advance and wait until you\'re ready for the sweets to begin pressing</string>
    <string name="french_macroons_desc">Though there is a common thought that making macrons will make you collapse on your kitchen floor, if you overcome that, you have a new world of taste before you.</string>
    <string name="brownie_ice_cream_desc">For an even faster version of this decadent ice-cream sandwich dessert, substitute your favorite brownie mix</string>
    <string name="frozen_yogurt_desc">Great for the kids—or the kids at heart—frozen fruit swirled into frozen yogurt and sandwiched between two crisp oatmeal cookies</string>
    <string name="ice_cream_desc">An ice cream sandwich is a frozen dessert consisting of ice cream between two wafers, cakes, cookies, or other similar biscuit</string>
    <string name="banana_nutella_desc">Yes, it\'s a Nutella and banana sandwich fried in butter. It\'s naughty, but we are allowed an occasional treat sometimes. Just make sure you go for a jog afterwards.</string>
    <string name="japanese_fruit_desc">Fruit sandwich are a very popular snack in Japan. These sandwiches are had during tea time in Japan. Mostly loved by women</string>
    <string name="fluffer_nutter_desc">The term “fluffernutter” was created by an advertising agency in 1960 as a more effective way to market the sandwich</string>
    <string name="peanut_jelly_desc">A 2002 survey showed the average American will have eaten 1,500 of these sandwiches before high school graduation</string>
    <string name="prosciutto_fig_desc">Prosciutto and fresh figs are a classic Italian combination. Along with the cheese and jam, they create a sweet-savory sandwich that's simple yet memorable.</string>
    <string name="cinnamon_toast_desc">Cinnamon Toast’s golden brown color, crispiness and ability to melt butter gets me every time. Warm and cozy.</string>

    <!-- GUILTY -->
    <string name="simple_tuna_melt_desc">Eating a late-night tuna melt in front of a woman is a sure sign you have completely stopped giving a crap. The taste speaks for itself</string>
    <string name="potato_chip_desc">A crisp sandwich, chip sandwich, chipwich, potato chip sandwich or chippy sandwich is a sandwich that includes crisps as one of the fillings</string>
    <string name="yakisoba_pan_desc">Pile the noodles into a bun sliced down the middle in the style of a hot dog, and garnish the top with mayonnaise and shreds of pickled ginger</string>
    <string name="fracesinha_desc">Daniel da Silva invented it in the 1960s when he tried to adapt the croque-monsieur to Portuguese taste. It is a very popular dish in Porto, Portugal.</string>
    <string name="roasted_turkey_desc"> It\'s a known fact that roasted turkey trumps deli turkey, so now\'s the time to make all your favorite turkey sandwiches</string>
    <string name="mexican_telera_desc">Telera refers to a Mexican bread similar to a French roll with a scored and flour-dusted crust. It can be found in Mexican markets</string>
    <string name="easy_slow_french_desc">Sometimes you create a recipe that’s so melt in your mouth –  savor every meaty, cheesy bite – delicious. This is one of them</string>
    <string name="porchetta_sandwich_desc">Porchetta is the body of a whole pig that’s been deboned, stuffed and roasted. It’s a popular dish from the Lazio region of Italy</string>
    <string name="chicken_biscuit_desc">Need a hearty, flavorful dinner? Why not whip up this scrumptious Spicy Chicken Breakfast biscuit?! Breakfast for dinner is the best!</string>
    <string name="meat_loaf_desc">Meatloaf is a lot like Thanksgiving turkey, it’s almost always better the day after. At least when sandwiched between two slices of bread.</string>
    <string name="cemitas_mexican_desc">The Cemita is what happens when a pulled pork sandwich spends Spring Break south of the border. This sandwich, a fan favorite in Puebla, Mexico</string>
    <string name="the_falafel_desc">Falafel is a deep fried ball or patty made from ground chickpeas, fava beans or both. It is commonly served in a pita, which acts as a pocket.</string>
    <string name="the_primanti_desc">You will be charmed by their incredibly over sized warm capicola sandwich stuffed with French fries and coleslaw</string>
    <string name="peanut_chicken_pitas_desc">Here's a tasty way to use up leftover roast chicken. Dark meat stands up to the intense flavors in the dressing</string>
    <string name="italian_beef_sandwich_desc">Italian Beef is made by slowly roasting lean beef on a rack above a pan filled with seasoned beef-based stock</string>
    <string name="sloppy_joe_desc">Make the sauce ahead of time, if you like. Just reheat it and toast the buns to finish the sliders</string>
    <string name="gatsby_sandwich_desc">Gatsbys originated in Cape Town, where people would often buy large rolls and fill them with whatever leftovers they had for lunch the next day</string>

    <!--=================VEGGIE=======================-->

    <string name="grilled_zucchini_desc">The fresh flavors in this Grilled Zucchini Caprese Sandwich recipe will leave you wanting more</string>
    <string name="caesar_salad_desc">Pack sandwich components separately the leaves and the cheese; a mixture of the dressing and pepper; and the toasted bagel</string>
    <string name="roasted_red_desc">If you like pimiento cheese, you'll enjoy this recipe. Keep the sandwiches well chilled so the cream cheese spread will remain firm</string>
    <string name="feta_basil_desc">Feta cheese, popularly used in mediterranean cuisine, has a slightly salty taste that goes well with the tomatoes and basil</string>
    <string name="tomato_basil_desc">Crusty Cuban bread is perfectly complemented with creamy mozzarella and a slice of juicy tomato. Serve with sweet potato chips or a simple green salad</string>
    <string name="veggie_hummus_desc">These flavorful wraps are filled with good-for-you ingredients like hummus and fresh vegetables. They're perfect for a quick lunch or dinner</string>
    <string name="open_eggplant_desc">Here's the key to a speedy dinner: While the eggplant broils, toast your bread slices in a toaster oven.</string>
    <string name="beet_brown_desc">These bite-size Beet and Brown Rice Sliders will leave you satisfied and craving another. Good news: a serving size of these veggie burgers is two sliders</string>
    <string name="farmers_market_desc">The stack of grilled eggplant, red onion, and zucchini are quite a mouthful but still tasty to eat. </string>
    <string name="baked_bean_desc">Good old toast and sandwiches never let you down. Try this and you are bound to love it. It is so simple and delicious</string>
    <string name="cucumber_sand_desc">The whole point about cucumber sandwiches is that, unless done really well, they're as dull as the sum of their ingredients</string>
    <string name="trini_doubles_desc">This popular breakfast food is also a late night favorite after a good "lime." "Lime" is the Trini term for "hanging out"</string>
    <string name="grilled_spaghetti_desc">Two favorite Italian foods, spaghetti and garlic bread, come together in this recipe which the whole family will love</string>
    <string name="spinach_feta_desc">Spinach is a natural with a grilled cheese. Plus, thanks to all of those Popeye cartoons when you were a kid, it makes you feel extra healthy</string>
    <string name="california_grilled_desc">Tasty and light, grilling gives the vegetables nice smoky taste. A little bit garlic and lemon juice brighten up the mayonnaise</string>
    <string name="mushroom_sand_desc">Mushrooms are an exceptionally nutrient-dense food, with one serve offering a surprising amount and array of essential nutrients</string>
    <string name="south_veggie_desc">A vegetarian (but trust me meat lovers, the meat is NOT missed in this one) packed wrap filled fresh veggies and a southwestern black-bean hummus</string>
    <string name="portabella_mushroom_desc">Mushrooms (especially portabellas!) are often used as a substitute for meat, not just for their texture, but for their umami (savory) flavor</string>
</resources>