<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!-- CLASSIC -->
    <string-array name="classic_blt_sandwich_dir">
        <item>Cook bacon until crispy, then drain on paper towels.</item>
        <item>Toast the 8 slices of bread.</item>
        <item>Spread 1 tablespoon mayo on each slice of toasted bread. (More or less, to taste).</item>
        <item>Add 1 slice of lettuce to 4 pieces of mayo-spread toast.</item>
        <item>Add 2 slices of tomato on top of lettuce.</item>
        <item>Arrange 3 slices of bacon evenly on top of tomato. (Break bacon slices in half to fit, if needed.).</item>
        <item>Add 1 slice of lettuce on top of bacon.</item>
        <item>Put the remaining 4 pieces of mayo-spread toast on top to finish the sandwiches.</item>
        <item>Enjoy!</item>
        <item>NOTE: I also like to butter the toast slices before adding the mayo, higher in fat, but tastier, in my opinion!</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="best_grilled_cheese_sandwich_dir">
        <item>Preheat oven to 350 degrees</item>
        <item>In a skillet, melt &#189; teaspoon of butter and add the red onion. Cook until softened, about 5 minutes. Set the onion aside.</item>
        <item>Place 2 slices of bread on your work surface. Top each with an equal amount of cheese. Top with the onions and place the remaining bread slices on top.</item>
        <item>Put 1 tablespoon butter in your skillet and cook on low heat to brown the butter. Be sure not to burn the butter.</item>
        <item>Add the sandwiches and cook until browned and toasty on the first side, about 1 &#189; minutes.</item>
        <item>Flip the sandwiches and cook for less than a minute.</item>
        <item>Remove the sandwiches from the skillet and place on a baking sheet. Spread the remaining butter on the sandwiches and place in the oven for 4 minutes, until everything is melted through.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="roasted_vegetable_sandwich_dir">
        <item>First, roast your pepper. All can be done at the same time. The red and green peppers.</item>
        <item>Heat the broiler.</item>
        <item>With tongs place the bell pepper on the top shelf turning often to get all sides blackened.</item>
        <item>It is a good idea to put a baking sheet on the rack below the peppers because when you go to turn them with your tongs juices can drip out.</item>
        <item>When the peppers are black, take them out of the over.</item>
        <item>Let cool and then rub off the blackened skin with a damp paper towel or peel with a paring knife if you are having trouble. Just grab an edge of the skin with the knife and peel off.</item>
        <item>Cut out the stem end and take out all of the pepper seeds. Set aside.</item>
        <item>While the peppers are roasting. Heat 1 tablespoon coconut oil in a skillet to medium heat.</item>
        <item>Add the onions and saute until the onions are translucent. About 10&#8211;15 minutes.</item>
        <item>You can also do the mushrooms at the same time. In fact, You can do all of this at the same time but you will dirty more pans. Do it all at once or do it back to back, overlapping a little.</item>
        <item>In a skillet heat 1 Tablespoon oil to medium high heat.</item>
        <item>Add the sliced sweet potatoes, brown on one side and then flip and brown on the other.</item>
        <item>Remove from heat and set aside.</item>
        <item>In the skillet add 1 Tablespoon oil and heat to medium high heat.</item>
        <item>Add the sliced mushrooms and saute for about 20 minutes. drain the liquid and then set aside.</item>
        <item>There you have all your prepared vegetables.</item>
        <item>Cut the rolls down the center and spread apart. Drizzle 1/8 cup of Italian dressing on each side of the rolls.</item>
        <item>Add any other condiment that you might like such as mustard or ketchup.</item>
        <item>Divide all the vegetable in layers between the four rolls.</item>
        <item>Add a lettuce layer of your favorite lettuce.</item>
        <item>Put the top on and take a big bite!</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="cuban_sandwich_dir">
        <item>Cut the bread in half lengthwise.</item>
        <item>Spread a thin layer of yellow mustard on the inside of each half of the bread.</item>
        <item>To assemble the sandwich, add a layer of pickles on the bottom piece of bread.</item>
        <item>Add the slices of roast pork, then add alternating layers of ham and cheese.</item>
        <item>Top with the other piece of bread.</item>
        <item>Spray a skillet, griddle, or sandwich press with cooking spray, like canola oil, and warm over medium-high heat.</item>
        <item>Place sandwich in pan and lightly spray top of the sandwich with canola oil or spread it with a little butter.</item>
        <item>Place a heavy weight on top of the sandwich, like a cast iron skillet, and press the sandwich.</item>
        <item>Cook the sandwich for about 4 minutes, then use a spatula to flip.</item>
        <item>Cook another 3 to 4 minutes, until the cheese is melted and the bread is toasted.</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--Luxe-->
    <string-array name="steak_foie_gras_dir">
        <item>Begin by preparing the foie mayo. Combine foie gras and mayonnaise in a blender until smooth.</item>
        <item>Adjust ratio to taste, and season with salt and pepper.</item>
        <item>Place in freezer for 5&#8211;10 minutes to chill.</item>
        <item>Heat griddle or skillet over medium heat.</item>
        <item>Cook steaks for about 5 minutes, chopping into smaller pieces, until slightly crispy.</item>
        <item>Lightly toast English muffins on griddle or in toaster.</item>
        <item>Add a slice of cheese to one side per sandwich and place under broiler until cheese is melted.</item>
        <item>To assemble sandwich, spread foie gras mayo on the cheese-less muffin half.</item>
        <item>Add steak and top with crumbled Cheetos and a dash of Aleppo pepper.</item>
        <item>Drizzle with pancake syrup.</item>
        <item>Top with cheesy muffin top and serve hot.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="crab_sandwich_dir">
        <item>Preheat broiler.</item>
        <item>In a bowl, combine crab meat, green onions, cheese, mayonnaise and cayenne (or hot pepper sauce).</item>
        <item>Slice tomatoes into eight slices.</item>
        <item>On a baking sheet or broiler pan place English muffin halves and broil 3&#8211;4 inches from heat until golden (3&#8211;5 minutes).</item>
        <item>Remove from oven.</item>
        <item>Place a tomato slice on each muffin half and top with crab mixture (about &#189; cup per muffin half).</item>
        <item>Sprinkle with extra shredded cheese, if desired.</item>
        <item>Return to oven and broil until cheese browns. (3&#8211;5 minutes).</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="caviar_quail_eggs_dir">
        <item>Place quail eggs in a medium saucepan, and cover with several inches of cold water.</item>
        <item>Bring to a boil, remove from heat, cover, and let sit for 4 minutes.</item>
        <item>Drain eggs, rinse with cold water, and allow to cool.</item>
        <item>Cut each egg in half and very gently remove yolks.</item>
        <item>Place yolk in a medium bowl with creme fraiche and mustard.</item>
        <item>Mash together until smooth.</item>
        <item>Taste and season with salt and pepper.</item>
        <item>Pipe yolk mixture into egg halves. (You can use a pastry bag or a plastic sandwich bag with the corner snipped off)</item>
        <item>Garnish top of each egg with caviar and chives.</item>
        <item>Place each egg on bread and serve them fresh.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="lobster_roll_dir">
        <item>Prepare a large ice-water bath.</item>
        <item>In a very large pot of boiling salted water, cook the lobsters until they turn bright red, about 10 minutes.</item>
        <item>Using tongs, plunge the lobsters into the ice-water bath for 2 minutes, then drain.</item>
        <item>Twist off the lobster tails and claws and remove the meat.</item>
        <item>Remove and discard the intestinal vein that runs the length of each lobster tail.</item>
        <item>Cut the lobster meat into &#189; inch pieces and pat dry, then transfer to a strainer set over a bowl and refrigerate until very cold, at least 1 hour.</item>
        <item>In a large bowl, mix the lobster meat with the mayonnaise and season with salt and pepper.</item>
        <item>Fold in the diced celery, lemon juice and cayenne pepper until well blended.</item>
        <item>Heat a large skillet.</item>
        <item>Brush the sides of the hot dog buns with the melted butter and toast over moderate heat until golden brown on both sides.</item>
        <item>Transfer the hot dog buns to plates, fill them with the shredded lettuce and the lobster salad and serve immediately.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="porteno_lomito_dir">
        <item>Bring pork roast to room temperature.</item>
        <item>Trim roast of excess fat.</item>
        <item>Season outside of roast with salt, pepper and oregano.</item>
        <item>In a large dutch oven brown roast all over.</item>
        <item>Place roast in a large roasting pan, along with the carrots, onion, garlic and celery.</item>
        <item>Add the chicken stock.</item>
        <item>Place in a preheated 400 degree oven and braise the roast for 2 hours or until the internal temperature is 160 degrees.</item>
        <item>Add water to braising liquid if  necessary. The braising liquid should be half way up the side of the roasting pan at all times.</item>
        <item>When pork is done Remove from braising liquid, and set aside.</item>
        <item>Using a wire mesh strainer, strain the braising liquid into a large stock pot.</item>
        <item>Over medium heat reduce strained liquid slightly. You should have about 4 cups.</item>
        <item>After pork roast has rested slice it very thinly.</item>
        <item>Add about &#189; lb of the sliced pork to each of 6 rolls.</item>
        <item>Smash the avocado and  spread onto pork.</item>
        <item>Add tomatoes and dress with a liberal amount of mayonnaise.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="bacon_nan_roll_dir">
        <item>Cook the bacon in a frying pan over a high heat until crisp, then drain on kitchen paper.</item>
        <item>Warm the naans a little in the oven.</item>
        <item>Spread one half of each naan with 1 tbsp each of cream cheese and chutney.</item>
        <item>Place the bacon on top.</item>
        <item>Sprinkle each with coriander and grind a little black pepper on top.</item>
        <item>Fold the other half of the naan over to create a semi-circle, and cut each naan in half.</item>
        <item>Makes two.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="open_sausage_dir">
        <item>Heat 1 Tbsp. oil in a large skillet over medium-high heat.</item>
        <item>Add sausages and cook, turning occasionally, until browned all over and cooked through, 8–10 minutes.</item>
        <item>Transfer to a cutting board and slice into &#189; inch pieces.</item>
        <item>Return sausage to skillet and add roasted peppers, vinegar, honey, cayenne, and remaining 1 Tbsp. oil.</item>
        <item>Cook, stirring occasionally, until peppers are warmed through and sauce is thickened, about 4 minutes.</item>
        <item>Stir in basil and season with salt and pepper.</item>
        <item>Divide sausage mixture evenly over toasted side of rolls.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="croque_monsieur_dir">
        <item>Melt 2 tablespoons butter in small saucepan over medium heat.</item>
        <item>Add flour and stir 1 minute. Gradually whisk in milk.</item>
        <item>Add nutmeg and bay leaf.</item>
        <item>Increase heat to medium-high and boil until sauce thickens, whisking constantly, about 2 minutes.</item>
        <item>Season with salt and pepper.</item>
        <item>Preheat broiler.</item>
        <item>Place 2 bread slices on work surface.</item>
        <item>Top each with half of ham and sliced Gruyère.</item>
        <item>Top with remaining bread.</item>
        <item>Heat heavy large skillet over low heat.</item>
        <item>Brush sandwiches with 1 tablespoon melted butter.</item>
        <item>Add to skillet and cook until deep golden brown, about 2 minutes per side.</item>
        <item>Transfer to small baking sheet.</item>
        <item>Spoon sauce, then grated cheese over sandwiches.</item>
        <item>Broil until cheese begins to brown, about 2 minutes.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="croque_madame_dir">
        <item>For the béchamel, melt half the butter in a small pan.</item>
        <item>Add the flour and stir over a medium heat until blended.</item>
        <item>Gradually add the milk, whisking continuously into a smooth sauce, then simmer gently for 2 to 3 minutes, or until the sauce has thickened.</item>
        <item>Add the mustard, nutmeg and sea salt and black pepper to taste. Set aside.</item>
        <item>Preheat the grill to high.</item>
        <item>Lightly toast the bread on both sides under the grill.</item>
        <item>Arrange slices of ham and cheese on each, then top with béchamel sauce.</item>
        <item>Place back under the grill to brown the béchamel and melt the cheese.</item>
        <item>Meanwhile, melt the remaining butter in a frying pan over a low heat.</item>
        <item>Crack in the egg and fry till the white is cooked but the yolk is still soft, or to your taste.</item>
        <item>Place the toasts on a plate and top with the egg.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="club_sandwich_dir">
        <item>Heat grill to High and cook the bacon, turning halfway through, until crisp.</item>
        <item>Toast the bread and spread one slice with the mayo.</item>
        <item>Layer on the egg, tomato and bacon, then top with another slice of bread.</item>
        <item>Add the chicken or turkey, bacon, then lettuce. Finish with the final slice of bread and cut into quarters.</item>
        <item>Secure with cocktail sticks and serve with crisps, if you like.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="pastrami_on_rye_dir">
        <item>Simmer pastrami in broth until hot.</item>
        <item>Divide meat among bread, using 4 ounces for smaller sandwich, and 8 ounces for large.</item>
        <item>Add cheese, mustard, pickles, and onions to taste.</item>
        <item>Grill sandwich until toasty and crisp if desired.</item>
        <item>Serve warm with chips if desired.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="veal_schnitzel_dir">
        <item>Heat 1 tablespoon oil in a large frying pan over high heat.</item>
        <item>Cook onion, stirring, for 4 to 5 minutes or until softened.</item>
        <item>Transfer to a plate.</item>
        <item>Heat remaining oil in pan over medium-high heat.</item>
        <item>Cook schnitzels for 2 minutes each side for medium or until cooked to your liking.</item>
        <item>Transfer to a plate line with paper towel.</item>
        <item>Meanwhile, cut bread into quarters. Split each piece in half.</item>
        <item>Toast until golden.</item>
        <item>Spread half the toast pieces with relish.</item>
        <item>Spread remaining pieces with mayonnaise.</item>
        <item>Place mayonnaise-topped pieces on plates.</item>
        <item>Top each with lettuce, tomato, schnitzel, onion and cheese.</item>
        <item>Sandwich with relish-topped toast.</item>
        <item>Cut in half.</item>
        <item>Serve.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="muffaletta_dir">
        <item>In a medium bowl, stir the pimento-stuffed olives with the giardiniera, capers and their respective liquids.</item>
        <item>Add the Calamata olives, garlic, shallot, oregano, parsley, thyme and crushed red pepper.</item>
        <item>Stir in the olive oil and let the mixture stand for 1 hour.</item>
        <item>Open the Italian bread on a work surface.</item>
        <item>Spoon the olive salad on both sides of the bread and spread evenly.</item>
        <item>Arrange the mozzarella slices on the bottom half of the bread, then top with the capocollo, Genoa salami and mortadella.</item>
        <item>Arrange the provolone cheese on the top half of the bread, covering the olive salad completely.</item>
        <item>Carefully close the sandwich.</item>
        <item>Wrap the sandwich tightly in plastic and let stand for 30 minutes or up to 2 hours.</item>
        <item>Cut the sandwich into 8 pieces and serve peperoncini on the side.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="smoked_eel_dir">
        <item>Begin by preparing the onion pickle.</item>
        <item>Combine the sugar and vinegar together in a pan and gently warm until dissolved.</item>
        <item>Remove from the heat and add the sliced onion to the pan, setting aside to steep for 1 hour.</item>
        <item>For the sandwich, place a griddle pan over a medium heat to warm up.</item>
        <item>Once hot, add the sourdough slice to the pan and grill on one side until brown.</item>
        <item>While the bread is toasting, slice the eel fillet into 3 even pieces.</item>
        <item>Remove the toasted sourdough, keeping the pan on the heat, and generously spread the toasted side of the bread first with butter followed by a little Dijon mustard.</item>
        <item>Slice the bread in half and top one half with the eel pieces followed by the horseradish cream.</item>
        <item>Place the other half on top (toasted side down) and return the sandwich to the griddle pan.</item>
        <item>Grill the sandwich on one side until brown, then flip carefully and grill for a further few minutes until golden and toasted.</item>
        <item>Drain the pickle and spoon onto a plate, adding the sandwich alongside it.</item>
        <item>Serve immediately.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="reuben_sandwich_dir">
        <item>Preheat a large skillet or griddle on medium heat.</item>
        <item>Lightly butter one side of bread slices.</item>
        <item>Spread non-buttered sides with Thousand Island dressing.</item>
        <item>On 4 bread slices, layer 1 slice Swiss cheese, 2 slices corned beef, &#188; cup sauerkraut and second slice of Swiss cheese.</item>
        <item>Top with remaining bread slices, buttered sides out.</item>
        <item>Grill sandwiches until both sides are golden brown, about 15 minutes per side.</item>
        <item>Serve hot.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="clam_roll_dir">
        <item>Preheat a grill.</item>
        <item>Combine the flour, corn flour, salt, and white pepper.</item>
        <item>Dip clams in evaporated milk then dredge in the seasoned flour mixture.</item>
        <item>Fill a deep pot halfway full with oil and heat to 350 degrees F.</item>
        <item>Fry the clams in the vegetable oil for approximately 1 to 2 minutes (depending on size), until golden brown.</item>
        <item>While clam strips are cooking, make the sauce.</item>
        <item>In a small mixing bowl, stir together the mayonnaise, minced dried onion, pickle relish, parsley and tarragon.</item>
        <item>Salt and pepper to taste.</item>
        <item>Cover and refrigerate until ready to use.</item>
        <item>Divide sauce evenly among the 4 rolls (it will be a generous amount).</item>
        <item>Top with clams and serve.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="hoisin_glazed_salmon_dir">
        <item>Combine the first 6 ingredients in a small saucepan; bring to a boil.</item>
        <item>Remove from heat; add cucumber.</item>
        <item>Let stand 30 minutes. Drain.</item>
        <item>Combine panko and the next 7 ingredients (through egg white) in a bowl, and stir well.</item>
        <item>Divide the mixture into 4 equal portions, gently shaping each into a &#189;-inch-thick patty.</item>
        <item>Press a nickel-sized indentation in the center of each patty.</item>
        <item>Heat a large cast-iron skillet over medium-high heat.</item>
        <item>Add sesame oil to pan; swirl to coat.</item>
        <item>Add patties; cook patties for 3 minutes on each side or until desired degree of done.</item>
        <item>Brush tops of patties evenly with hoisin; cook for 30 seconds.</item>
        <item>Place 1 patty on bottom half of each bun; top each patty with 6 cucumber slices and top half of bun.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="pan_bagnat_dir">
        <item>In a small bowl, whisk together the optional anchovies, the garlic, vinegar, mustard, salt and pepper.</item>
        <item>Slowly drizzle in oil, whisking constantly.</item>
        <item>If using a country loaf, pull out some soft interior crumb to form a cavity.</item>
        <item>If using a ciabatta, you won't need to eliminate anything.</item>
        <item>If using a Kirby cucumber, slice thinly.</item>
        <item>If using a regular cucumber, peel, halve lengthwise, and scoop out seeds from one half.</item>
        <item>Thinly slice seedless half.</item>
        <item>Add sliced cucumber to vinaigrette and toss well.</item>
        <item>Spread half the cucumbers on bottom of bread.</item>
        <item>Top with tomato and onion slices, then with tuna, basil, olives and egg slices.</item>
        <item>Top egg with remaining cucumbers and vinaigrette.</item>
        <item>Cover with second bread half and firmly press sandwich together.</item>
        <item>Wrap sandwich tightly in foil, waxed paper or plastic wrap, then place in a plastic bag.</item>
        <item>Put sandwich under a weight such as a cast-iron frying pan topped with a filled kettle, or have a child about 7 years old sit on it.</item>
        <item>Weight sandwich for 7 to 10 minutes, then flip and weight it for another 7 to 10 minutes (or as long as you can get the child to sit still).</item>
        <item>Unwrap, slice and serve immediately, or keep it wrapped for up to 8 hours before serving.</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- GUILTY -->
    <string-array name="simple_tuna_melt_dir">
        <item>Preheat the oven to 375 degrees F (190 degrees C).</item>
        <item>Place bread slices in the oven to toast while it preheats, and while you make the tuna salad.</item>
        <item>In a small bowl, mix together the tuna, mayonnaise, salt, balsamic vinegar, mustard and dill pickle until well blended.</item>
        <item>Remove bread from the oven, and pile the tuna mixture onto one slice.</item>
        <item>Sprinkle cheese over the other slice of bread.</item>
        <item>Bake for 7 minutes in the preheated oven, or until cheese is melted and tuna is heated through.</item>
        <item>Place the cheese side of the sandwich on top of the tuna side.</item>
        <item>Cut in half and serve immediately.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>