<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!-- CLASSIC -->
    <string-array name="classic_blt_sandwich_dir">
        <item>Cook bacon until crispy, then drain on paper towels.</item>
        <item>Toast the 8 slices of bread.</item>
        <item>Spread 1 tablespoon mayo on each slice of toasted bread. (More or less, to taste).</item>
        <item>Add 1 slice of lettuce to 4 pieces of mayo-spread toast.</item>
        <item>Add 2 slices of tomato on top of lettuce.</item>
        <item>Arrange 3 slices of bacon evenly on top of tomato. (Break bacon slices in half to fit, if needed.).</item>
        <item>Add 1 slice of lettuce on top of bacon.</item>
        <item>Put the remaining 4 pieces of mayo-spread toast on top to finish the sandwiches.</item>
        <item>Enjoy!</item>
        <item>NOTE: I also like to butter the toast slices before adding the mayo, higher in fat, but tastier, in my opinion!</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="best_grilled_cheese_sandwich_dir">
        <item>Preheat oven to 350 degrees</item>
        <item>In a skillet, melt &#189; teaspoon of butter and add the red onion. Cook until softened, about 5 minutes. Set the onion aside.</item>
        <item>Place 2 slices of bread on your work surface. Top each with an equal amount of cheese. Top with the onions and place the remaining bread slices on top.</item>
        <item>Put 1 tablespoon butter in your skillet and cook on low heat to brown the butter. Be sure not to burn the butter.</item>
        <item>Add the sandwiches and cook until browned and toasty on the first side, about 1 &#189; minutes.</item>
        <item>Flip the sandwiches and cook for less than a minute.</item>
        <item>Remove the sandwiches from the skillet and place on a baking sheet. Spread the remaining butter on the sandwiches and place in the oven for 4 minutes, until everything is melted through.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="roasted_vegetable_sandwich_dir">
        <item>First, roast your pepper. All can be done at the same time. The red and green peppers.</item>
        <item>Heat the broiler.</item>
        <item>With tongs place the bell pepper on the top shelf turning often to get all sides blackened.</item>
        <item>It is a good idea to put a baking sheet on the rack below the peppers because when you go to turn them with your tongs juices can drip out.</item>
        <item>When the peppers are black, take them out of the over.</item>
        <item>Let cool and then rub off the blackened skin with a damp paper towel or peel with a paring knife if you are having trouble. Just grab an edge of the skin with the knife and peel off.</item>
        <item>Cut out the stem end and take out all of the pepper seeds. Set aside.</item>
        <item>While the peppers are roasting. Heat 1 tablespoon coconut oil in a skillet to medium heat.</item>
        <item>Add the onions and saute until the onions are translucent. About 10&#8211;15 minutes.</item>
        <item>You can also do the mushrooms at the same time. In fact, You can do all of this at the same time but you will dirty more pans. Do it all at once or do it back to back, overlapping a little.</item>
        <item>In a skillet heat 1 Tablespoon oil to medium high heat.</item>
        <item>Add the sliced sweet potatoes, brown on one side and then flip and brown on the other.</item>
        <item>Remove from heat and set aside.</item>
        <item>In the skillet add 1 Tablespoon oil and heat to medium high heat.</item>
        <item>Add the sliced mushrooms and saute for about 20 minutes. drain the liquid and then set aside.</item>
        <item>There you have all your prepared vegetables.</item>
        <item>Cut the rolls down the center and spread apart. Drizzle 1/8 cup of Italian dressing on each side of the rolls.</item>
        <item>Add any other condiment that you might like such as mustard or ketchup.</item>
        <item>Divide all the vegetable in layers between the four rolls.</item>
        <item>Add a lettuce layer of your favorite lettuce.</item>
        <item>Put the top on and take a big bite!</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="cuban_sandwich_dir">
        <item>Cut the bread in half lengthwise.</item>
        <item>Spread a thin layer of yellow mustard on the inside of each half of the bread.</item>
        <item>To assemble the sandwich, add a layer of pickles on the bottom piece of bread.</item>
        <item>Add the slices of roast pork, then add alternating layers of ham and cheese.</item>
        <item>Top with the other piece of bread.</item>
        <item>Spray a skillet, griddle, or sandwich press with cooking spray, like canola oil, and warm over medium-high heat.</item>
        <item>Place sandwich in pan and lightly spray top of the sandwich with canola oil or spread it with a little butter.</item>
        <item>Place a heavy weight on top of the sandwich, like a cast iron skillet, and press the sandwich.</item>
        <item>Cook the sandwich for about 4 minutes, then use a spatula to flip.</item>
        <item>Cook another 3 to 4 minutes, until the cheese is melted and the bread is toasted.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="bombay_vada_pav_dir">
        <item>To make the batter place the gram flour in a bowl.</item>
        <item>Add salt, red chili powder, turmeric powder, soda bicarbonate and mix.</item>
        <item>Add sufficient water and whip to a smooth and thick batter.</item>
        <item>Set aside for at least fifteen minutes.</item>
        <item>Place the boiled potatoes in a bowl.</item>
        <item>Heat one tablespoon oil in a pan.</item>
        <item>Add asafoetida, turmeric powder, green chili-garlic paste and mix.</item>
        <item>Add potatoes and salt and mix.</item>
        <item>Set aside to cool.</item>
        <item>Add coriander leaves, lemon juice and mix mashing the potatoes some more.</item>
        <item>Divide the mixture into eight equal portions and shape them into balls.</item>
        <item>Heat sufficient oil in a deep frying pan.</item>
        <item>Dip the potato balls in the chickpea flour batter and deep fry till golden and crisp on the outside.</item>
        <item>Drain on absorbent paper.</item>
        <item>Slit each pav, spread some dry garlic chutney, place a vada and press lightly.</item>
        <item>Serve immediately.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="cheese_steak_dir">
        <item>Heat a griddle or a large saute pan over medium-high heat.</item>
        <item>When hot, cover bottom with olive oil.</item>
        <item>Add the onions and bell pepper and cook, stirring, until carmelized, which will take about 6 to 8 minutes.</item>
        <item>Add the garlic, salt and pepper, and cook for about 30 seconds.</item>
        <item>Then, push the mixture off to one side of the griddle.</item>
        <item>Add the meat to the hot part of the griddle.</item>
        <item>Cook, continuously flipping the meat over and slightly chopping the meat into slightly smaller pieces with 2 spatulas, until the meat is not pink, which should take about 2 minutes.</item>
        <item>Mix the meat and the carmelized onions and bell pepper together.</item>
        <item>Divide into 2 portions, and top both portions with the cheese to melt.</item>
        <item>If using Italian or French bread, cut the bread in half, crosswise, and slice lengthwise to open for the 2 sandwiches.</item>
        <item>Hollow out some of the soft white bread part from inside and place face down on top of the meat and cheese.</item>
        <item>When the cheese is melted, and with 1 or 2 spatulas, flip the sandwiches over and add topping, such as marinara sauce or ketchup, if desired, and serve immediately.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="shripm_po_dir">
        <item>Preheat 1-inch of oil in a deep skillet over medium to medium-high heat.</item>
        <item>Beat egg and milk together.</item>
        <item>Pull tails off shrimp. Salt shrimp then soak in milk batter.</item>
        <item>Before you begin breading the shrimp, cover a plate with plastic wrap for easy clean up then mix together the flour, cornmeal or bread crumbs and seafood seasoning on the plate.</item>
        <item>Using tongs, remove a few shrimp at a time and coat in breading.</item>
        <item>Add breaded shrimp to the hot oil and fry them 5 to 6 minutes or until firm and deeply golden all over.</item>
        <item>Pile lettuce and tomato on rolls and top with shrimp, douse the shrimp with a little lemon juice.</item>
        <item>Mix relish, mustard and hot sauce and dot the roll tops with spoonfuls of the sauce before setting into place.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="italian_hero_dir">
        <item>In a small bowl, combine the vinegar, oregano, mustard, salt and pepper.</item>
        <item>Stir to mix well.</item>
        <item>Whisk in the olive oil until incorporated.</item>
        <item>On a work surface, lay out 3 long pieces of plastic wrap, placing them side by side and slightly overlapping.</item>
        <item>Place the bottom half of the loaf over the wrap.</item>
        <item>Spread the pepperoncini and cherry peppers over the bread.</item>
        <item>Scatter evenly with the lettuce and layer with the tomatoes.</item>
        <item>Drizzle with a few tablespoons of the dressing.</item>
        <item>Layer the meats, one at a time, over the tomatoes, making sure to distribute them evenly.</item>
        <item>Top with a layer of provolone cheese.</item>
        <item>Drizzle the remaining dressing over the cut side of the top of the loaf.</item>
        <item>Place on the layered sandwich and enclose in the plastic.</item>
        <item>Refrigerate for at least 1 hour or for up to 4 hours to develop the flavors.</item>
        <item>To serve, unwrap the sandwich and slice into large pieces about 3 to 4 inches wide.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="meatball_sub_dir">
        <item>Preheat the oven to 350 degrees F (175 degrees C).</item>
        <item>In a medium bowl, gently mix by hand the ground beef, bread crumbs, Italian seasoning, garlic, parsley, Parmesan cheese, and egg.</item>
        <item>Shape into 12 meatballs, and place in a baking dish.</item>
        <item>Bake for 15 to 20 minutes in the preheated oven, or until cooked through.</item>
        <item>Meanwhile, cut the baguette in half lengthwise, and remove some of the bread from the inside to make a well for the meatballs.</item>
        <item>Brush with olive oil, and season with garlic powder and salt.</item>
        <item>Slip the baguette into the oven during the last 5 minutes of the meatball's time, or until lightly toasted.</item>
        <item>While the bread toasts, warm the spaghetti sauce in a saucepan over medium heat.</item>
        <item>When the meatballs are done, use a slotted spoon to transfer them to the sauce.</item>
        <item>Spoon onto the baguette and top with slices of provolone cheese.</item>
        <item>Return to the oven for 2 to 3 minutes to melt the cheese.</item>
        <item>Cool slightly, cut into servings, and enjoy!</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="patty_melt_dir">
        <item>In a medium skillet, melt 2 tablespoons of the butter over medium-low heat.</item>
        <item>Throw in the sliced onions and cook slowly until the onions are golden brown and soft, 20 to 25 minutes, stirring occasionally.</item>
        <item>In a medium bowl, mix together the ground beef, Worcestershire and some salt and pepper.</item>
        <item>Form into 4 patties.</item>
        <item>Melt 2 tablespoons of the butter in a separate skillet over medium heat.</item>
        <item>Cook the patties on both sides until totally done in the middle.</item>
        <item>Assemble the patty melts this way: Slice of bread, slice of cheese, hamburger patty, a quarter of the cooked onions, another slice of cheese and another slice of bread.</item>
        <item>On a clean griddle or in a large skillet over medium heat, melt 2 tablespoons of the butter and grill the sandwiches until golden brown.</item>
        <item>Remove the sandwiches and add the remaining 2 tablespoons butter to the skillet.</item>
        <item>Return the sandwiches to the skillet, flipping them to the other side.</item>
        <item>Cook until golden brown and crisp, and until the cheese is melted.</item>
        <item>Slice in half and serve immediately!</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="fish_fillet_dir">
        <item>Preheat oven to 350'.</item>
        <item>Place a baking sheet in oven and let heat up for a good 20 to 25 minutes.</item>
        <item>Set up a breading station with 3 separate deep bowls or containers.</item>
        <item>Add flour, kosher salt and black pepper to one containter and set aside.</item>
        <item>In the 2nd containter, add egg and milk , whipped up together and adding a touch of salt and black pepper , and set aside.</item>
        <item>In the 3rd containter add Panko breadcrumbs with more salt and black pepper.</item>
        <item>Cut halibut tail into 2 pieces.</item>
        <item>Dip each halibut fillet into the flour mixture first than into the egg mixture, and than into the panko breading.</item>
        <item>Set each fillet onto a cutting board or a plate to let rest 5 minutes.</item>
        <item>Bring out baking sheet from oven and sprinkle some olive oil over the pan.</item>
        <item>Place halibut fillets on hot baking sheet ( it should sizzle when placing on sheet).</item>
        <item>Bake 30 minutes or until a golden brown.</item>
        <item>Split open the french bread and spread butter over each slice of french bread.</item>
        <item>Toast bread in oven until a light golden brown.</item>
        <item>Add tarter sauce to each toasted side of bread.</item>
        <item>Add the fish fillet to one side of bread.</item>
        <item>Add avocado, tomato and romaine lettuce on top of fish.</item>
        <item>Top with other side of bread and serve.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="kentuky_hot_dir">
        <item>In a large skillet, melt &#189; cup butter over medium heat.</item>
        <item>Stir in enough flour to absorb all of the butter.</item>
        <item>Slowly whisk in the milk, and 6 tablespoons of Parmesan cheese.</item>
        <item>Stir in the egg to thicken the sauce, but do not allow to boil.</item>
        <item>Remove from heat, and season with salt and pepper to taste.</item>
        <item>Heat remaining tablespoon of butter in a small skillet.</item>
        <item>Saute mushrooms in the butter until soft. Set aside.</item>
        <item>Preheat your oven's broiler.</item>
        <item>For each Hot Brown, place two slices of toast onto a heatproof plate or dish.</item>
        <item>Cover the toast with about &#188; cup sauteed mushrooms and a couple of tomato slices.</item>
        <item>Place a liberal amount of turkey onto each Hot Brown, and pour an even more liberal amount of sauce over.</item>
        <item>Smother that baby.</item>
        <item>Sprinkle remaining Parmesan cheese over the top.</item>
        <item>Repeat with remaining ingredients.</item>
        <item>Place the entire dish under the broiler until the sauce is speckled brown and bubbly.</item>
        <item>Remove from broiler, criss-cross two slices of bacon on top, and serve!</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="the_elvis_dir">
        <item>Spread the peanut butter on one side of one slice of bread.</item>
        <item>Top with sliced banana, then slices of cooked bacon.</item>
        <item>Cover with the other slice of bread.</item>
        <item>Spread butter on the outside of the sandwich.</item>
        <item>Heat a skillet over medium heat.</item>
        <item>Fry the sandwich on each side until golden brown and peanut butter is melted, about 4 minutes total.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="fried_bologna_dir">
        <item>Put oil in a frying pan and heat to med. high.</item>
        <item>Put slit in bologna from middle to all the way through the end.</item>
        <item>Put bologna in heated oil.</item>
        <item>Brown both sides.</item>
        <item>Add cheese to top while last side is browning.</item>
        <item>Spread mustard on both sides of bread.</item>
        <item>Add bologna between slices and gobble it up!</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="open_chicken_dir">
        <item>Heat a large skillet over medium-high heat.</item>
        <item>Add oil to pan; swirl to coat.</item>
        <item>Sprinkle chicken evenly with 1/8 teaspoon salt and pepper.</item>
        <item>Add chicken to pan; sauté 6 minutes on each side or until done.</item>
        <item>Remove from pan; let stand 5 minutes. Slice.</item>
        <item>Combine remaining 1/8 teaspoon salt, juice, mayonnaise, and avocado in a small bowl; stir until well blended.</item>
        <item>Spread about 3 tablespoons avocado mixture over each bread slice.</item>
        <item>Top each sandwich with 1 lettuce leaf, 1 chicken breast half, 3 tomato slices, and 1 bacon slice.</item>
        <item>Serve</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="chicken_waffle_dir">
        <item>Cook bacon in a large nonstick skillet over medium heat until crisp.</item>
        <item>Drain on paper towels.</item>
        <item>Combine mayonnaise and the next 5 ingredients (through black pepper) in a small bowl.</item>
        <item>Spread mayonnaise mixture evenly over 4 waffles.</item>
        <item>Divide chicken, bacon, tomato, and lettuce evenly among servings.</item>
        <item>Top with remaining waffles.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="jambon_beurre_dir">
        <item>Spread the butter on cut sides of the baguette.</item>
        <item>Add the cheese (if using) to the bottom slice and top with the ham.</item>
        <item>Top with the other slice of baguette.</item>
        <item>Cut the sandwich into two equal parts.</item>
        <item>Serve or refrigerate (wrapped in plastic) for up to one day!</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="creamed_eggs_dir">
        <item>Separate the egg whites from the egg yolks.</item>
        <item>Place the egg yolks into a bowl and mash with a fork.</item>
        <item>Chop the egg whites into small pieces and set aside.</item>
        <item>Melt the butter in a saucepan set over medium heat.</item>
        <item>Stir in flour until smooth.</item>
        <item>Gradually mix in the milk and chicken bouillon so that no lumps form and stir constantly until the mixture comes to a boil.</item>
        <item>Add the egg yolks and mix until dissolved.</item>
        <item>Stir in egg whites.</item>
        <item>Serve over toast and season with salt and white pepper.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="chicken_parmesan_dir">
        <item>Position oven rack in top position; preheat broiler.</item>
        <item>Combine flour, salt and pepper in a shallow dish.</item>
        <item>Place chicken between 2 large pieces of plastic wrap.</item>
        <item>Pound with the smooth side of a meat mallet or a heavy saucepan until the chicken is an even &#188; inch thickness.</item>
        <item>Dip the chicken in the flour mixture and turn to coat.</item>
        <item>Heat 2 teaspoons oil in a large nonstick skillet over medium-high heat.</item>
        <item>Add spinach and cook, stirring often, until wilted, 2 to 3 minutes. Transfer to a small bowl.</item>
        <item>Add 1 teaspoon oil to the pan.</item>
        <item>Add half the chicken and cook until golden, 1 to 2 minutes per side.</item>
        <item>Transfer to a large baking sheet.</item>
        <item>Repeat with the remaining 1 teaspoon oil and chicken; transfer to the baking sheet.</item>
        <item>Top each piece of chicken with the wilted spinach, marinara sauce and Parmesan.</item>
        <item>Sprinkle with mozzarella.</item>
        <item>Broil until the cheese is melted and the chicken is cooked through, about 3 minutes.</item>
        <item>Serve on rolls.</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--===================Luxe=========================-->
    <string-array name="steak_foie_gras_dir">
        <item>Begin by preparing the foie mayo. Combine foie gras and mayonnaise in a blender until smooth.</item>
        <item>Adjust ratio to taste, and season with salt and pepper.</item>
        <item>Place in freezer for 5&#8211;10 minutes to chill.</item>
        <item>Heat griddle or skillet over medium heat.</item>
        <item>Cook steaks for about 5 minutes, chopping into smaller pieces, until slightly crispy.</item>
        <item>Lightly toast English muffins on griddle or in toaster.</item>
        <item>Add a slice of cheese to one side per sandwich and place under broiler until cheese is melted.</item>
        <item>To assemble sandwich, spread foie gras mayo on the cheese-less muffin half.</item>
        <item>Add steak and top with crumbled Cheetos and a dash of Aleppo pepper.</item>
        <item>Drizzle with pancake syrup.</item>
        <item>Top with cheesy muffin top and serve hot.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="crab_sandwich_dir">
        <item>Preheat broiler.</item>
        <item>In a bowl, combine crab meat, green onions, cheese, mayonnaise and cayenne (or hot pepper sauce).</item>
        <item>Slice tomatoes into eight slices.</item>
        <item>On a baking sheet or broiler pan place English muffin halves and broil 3&#8211;4 inches from heat until golden (3&#8211;5 minutes).</item>
        <item>Remove from oven.</item>
        <item>Place a tomato slice on each muffin half and top with crab mixture (about &#189; cup per muffin half).</item>
        <item>Sprinkle with extra shredded cheese, if desired.</item>
        <item>Return to oven and broil until cheese browns. (3&#8211;5 minutes).</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="caviar_quail_eggs_dir">
        <item>Place quail eggs in a medium saucepan, and cover with several inches of cold water.</item>
        <item>Bring to a boil, remove from heat, cover, and let sit for 4 minutes.</item>
        <item>Drain eggs, rinse with cold water, and allow to cool.</item>
        <item>Cut each egg in half and very gently remove yolks.</item>
        <item>Place yolk in a medium bowl with creme fraiche and mustard.</item>
        <item>Mash together until smooth.</item>
        <item>Taste and season with salt and pepper.</item>
        <item>Pipe yolk mixture into egg halves. (You can use a pastry bag or a plastic sandwich bag with the corner snipped off)</item>
        <item>Garnish top of each egg with caviar and chives.</item>
        <item>Place each egg on bread and serve them fresh.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="lobster_roll_dir">
        <item>Prepare a large ice-water bath.</item>
        <item>In a very large pot of boiling salted water, cook the lobsters until they turn bright red, about 10 minutes.</item>
        <item>Using tongs, plunge the lobsters into the ice-water bath for 2 minutes, then drain.</item>
        <item>Twist off the lobster tails and claws and remove the meat.</item>
        <item>Remove and discard the intestinal vein that runs the length of each lobster tail.</item>
        <item>Cut the lobster meat into &#189; inch pieces and pat dry, then transfer to a strainer set over a bowl and refrigerate until very cold, at least 1 hour.</item>
        <item>In a large bowl, mix the lobster meat with the mayonnaise and season with salt and pepper.</item>
        <item>Fold in the diced celery, lemon juice and cayenne pepper until well blended.</item>
        <item>Heat a large skillet.</item>
        <item>Brush the sides of the hot dog buns with the melted butter and toast over moderate heat until golden brown on both sides.</item>
        <item>Transfer the hot dog buns to plates, fill them with the shredded lettuce and the lobster salad and serve immediately.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="porteno_lomito_dir">
        <item>Bring pork roast to room temperature.</item>
        <item>Trim roast of excess fat.</item>
        <item>Season outside of roast with salt, pepper and oregano.</item>
        <item>In a large dutch oven brown roast all over.</item>
        <item>Place roast in a large roasting pan, along with the carrots, onion, garlic and celery.</item>
        <item>Add the chicken stock.</item>
        <item>Place in a preheated 400 degree oven and braise the roast for 2 hours or until the internal temperature is 160 degrees.</item>
        <item>Add water to braising liquid if  necessary. The braising liquid should be half way up the side of the roasting pan at all times.</item>
        <item>When pork is done Remove from braising liquid, and set aside.</item>
        <item>Using a wire mesh strainer, strain the braising liquid into a large stock pot.</item>
        <item>Over medium heat reduce strained liquid slightly. You should have about 4 cups.</item>
        <item>After pork roast has rested slice it very thinly.</item>
        <item>Add about &#189; lb of the sliced pork to each of 6 rolls.</item>
        <item>Smash the avocado and  spread onto pork.</item>
        <item>Add tomatoes and dress with a liberal amount of mayonnaise.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="bacon_nan_roll_dir">
        <item>Cook the bacon in a frying pan over a high heat until crisp, then drain on kitchen paper.</item>
        <item>Warm the naans a little in the oven.</item>
        <item>Spread one half of each naan with 1 tbsp each of cream cheese and chutney.</item>
        <item>Place the bacon on top.</item>
        <item>Sprinkle each with coriander and grind a little black pepper on top.</item>
        <item>Fold the other half of the naan over to create a semi-circle, and cut each naan in half.</item>
        <item>Makes two.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="open_sausage_dir">
        <item>Heat 1 Tbsp. oil in a large skillet over medium-high heat.</item>
        <item>Add sausages and cook, turning occasionally, until browned all over and cooked through, 8–10 minutes.</item>
        <item>Transfer to a cutting board and slice into &#189; inch pieces.</item>
        <item>Return sausage to skillet and add roasted peppers, vinegar, honey, cayenne, and remaining 1 Tbsp. oil.</item>
        <item>Cook, stirring occasionally, until peppers are warmed through and sauce is thickened, about 4 minutes.</item>
        <item>Stir in basil and season with salt and pepper.</item>
        <item>Divide sausage mixture evenly over toasted side of rolls.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="croque_monsieur_dir">
        <item>Melt 2 tablespoons butter in small saucepan over medium heat.</item>
        <item>Add flour and stir 1 minute. Gradually whisk in milk.</item>
        <item>Add nutmeg and bay leaf.</item>
        <item>Increase heat to medium-high and boil until sauce thickens, whisking constantly, about 2 minutes.</item>
        <item>Season with salt and pepper.</item>
        <item>Preheat broiler.</item>
        <item>Place 2 bread slices on work surface.</item>
        <item>Top each with half of ham and sliced Gruyère.</item>
        <item>Top with remaining bread.</item>
        <item>Heat heavy large skillet over low heat.</item>
        <item>Brush sandwiches with 1 tablespoon melted butter.</item>
        <item>Add to skillet and cook until deep golden brown, about 2 minutes per side.</item>
        <item>Transfer to small baking sheet.</item>
        <item>Spoon sauce, then grated cheese over sandwiches.</item>
        <item>Broil until cheese begins to brown, about 2 minutes.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="croque_madame_dir">
        <item>For the béchamel, melt half the butter in a small pan.</item>
        <item>Add the flour and stir over a medium heat until blended.</item>
        <item>Gradually add the milk, whisking continuously into a smooth sauce, then simmer gently for 2 to 3 minutes, or until the sauce has thickened.</item>
        <item>Add the mustard, nutmeg and sea salt and black pepper to taste. Set aside.</item>
        <item>Preheat the grill to high.</item>
        <item>Lightly toast the bread on both sides under the grill.</item>
        <item>Arrange slices of ham and cheese on each, then top with béchamel sauce.</item>
        <item>Place back under the grill to brown the béchamel and melt the cheese.</item>
        <item>Meanwhile, melt the remaining butter in a frying pan over a low heat.</item>
        <item>Crack in the egg and fry till the white is cooked but the yolk is still soft, or to your taste.</item>
        <item>Place the toasts on a plate and top with the egg.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="club_sandwich_dir">
        <item>Heat grill to High and cook the bacon, turning halfway through, until crisp.</item>
        <item>Toast the bread and spread one slice with the mayo.</item>
        <item>Layer on the egg, tomato and bacon, then top with another slice of bread.</item>
        <item>Add the chicken or turkey, bacon, then lettuce. Finish with the final slice of bread and cut into quarters.</item>
        <item>Secure with cocktail sticks and serve with crisps, if you like.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="pastrami_on_rye_dir">
        <item>Simmer pastrami in broth until hot.</item>
        <item>Divide meat among bread, using 4 ounces for smaller sandwich, and 8 ounces for large.</item>
        <item>Add cheese, mustard, pickles, and onions to taste.</item>
        <item>Grill sandwich until toasty and crisp if desired.</item>
        <item>Serve warm with chips if desired.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="veal_schnitzel_dir">
        <item>Heat 1 tablespoon oil in a large frying pan over high heat.</item>
        <item>Cook onion, stirring, for 4 to 5 minutes or until softened.</item>
        <item>Transfer to a plate.</item>
        <item>Heat remaining oil in pan over medium-high heat.</item>
        <item>Cook schnitzels for 2 minutes each side for medium or until cooked to your liking.</item>
        <item>Transfer to a plate line with paper towel.</item>
        <item>Meanwhile, cut bread into quarters. Split each piece in half.</item>
        <item>Toast until golden.</item>
        <item>Spread half the toast pieces with relish.</item>
        <item>Spread remaining pieces with mayonnaise.</item>
        <item>Place mayonnaise-topped pieces on plates.</item>
        <item>Top each with lettuce, tomato, schnitzel, onion and cheese.</item>
        <item>Sandwich with relish-topped toast.</item>
        <item>Cut in half.</item>
        <item>Serve.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="muffaletta_dir">
        <item>In a medium bowl, stir the pimento-stuffed olives with the giardiniera, capers and their respective liquids.</item>
        <item>Add the Calamata olives, garlic, shallot, oregano, parsley, thyme and crushed red pepper.</item>
        <item>Stir in the olive oil and let the mixture stand for 1 hour.</item>
        <item>Open the Italian bread on a work surface.</item>
        <item>Spoon the olive salad on both sides of the bread and spread evenly.</item>
        <item>Arrange the mozzarella slices on the bottom half of the bread, then top with the capocollo, Genoa salami and mortadella.</item>
        <item>Arrange the provolone cheese on the top half of the bread, covering the olive salad completely.</item>
        <item>Carefully close the sandwich.</item>
        <item>Wrap the sandwich tightly in plastic and let stand for 30 minutes or up to 2 hours.</item>
        <item>Cut the sandwich into 8 pieces and serve peperoncini on the side.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="smoked_eel_dir">
        <item>Begin by preparing the onion pickle.</item>
        <item>Combine the sugar and vinegar together in a pan and gently warm until dissolved.</item>
        <item>Remove from the heat and add the sliced onion to the pan, setting aside to steep for 1 hour.</item>
        <item>For the sandwich, place a griddle pan over a medium heat to warm up.</item>
        <item>Once hot, add the sourdough slice to the pan and grill on one side until brown.</item>
        <item>While the bread is toasting, slice the eel fillet into 3 even pieces.</item>
        <item>Remove the toasted sourdough, keeping the pan on the heat, and generously spread the toasted side of the bread first with butter followed by a little Dijon mustard.</item>
        <item>Slice the bread in half and top one half with the eel pieces followed by the horseradish cream.</item>
        <item>Place the other half on top (toasted side down) and return the sandwich to the griddle pan.</item>
        <item>Grill the sandwich on one side until brown, then flip carefully and grill for a further few minutes until golden and toasted.</item>
        <item>Drain the pickle and spoon onto a plate, adding the sandwich alongside it.</item>
        <item>Serve immediately.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="reuben_sandwich_dir">
        <item>Preheat a large skillet or griddle on medium heat.</item>
        <item>Lightly butter one side of bread slices.</item>
        <item>Spread non-buttered sides with Thousand Island dressing.</item>
        <item>On 4 bread slices, layer 1 slice Swiss cheese, 2 slices corned beef, &#188; cup sauerkraut and second slice of Swiss cheese.</item>
        <item>Top with remaining bread slices, buttered sides out.</item>
        <item>Grill sandwiches until both sides are golden brown, about 15 minutes per side.</item>
        <item>Serve hot.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="clam_roll_dir">
        <item>Preheat a grill.</item>
        <item>Combine the flour, corn flour, salt, and white pepper.</item>
        <item>Dip clams in evaporated milk then dredge in the seasoned flour mixture.</item>
        <item>Fill a deep pot halfway full with oil and heat to 350 degrees F.</item>
        <item>Fry the clams in the vegetable oil for approximately 1 to 2 minutes (depending on size), until golden brown.</item>
        <item>While clam strips are cooking, make the sauce.</item>
        <item>In a small mixing bowl, stir together the mayonnaise, minced dried onion, pickle relish, parsley and tarragon.</item>
        <item>Salt and pepper to taste.</item>
        <item>Cover and refrigerate until ready to use.</item>
        <item>Divide sauce evenly among the 4 rolls (it will be a generous amount).</item>
        <item>Top with clams and serve.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="hoisin_glazed_salmon_dir">
        <item>Combine the first 6 ingredients in a small saucepan; bring to a boil.</item>
        <item>Remove from heat; add cucumber.</item>
        <item>Let stand 30 minutes. Drain.</item>
        <item>Combine panko and the next 7 ingredients (through egg white) in a bowl, and stir well.</item>
        <item>Divide the mixture into 4 equal portions, gently shaping each into a &#189;-inch-thick patty.</item>
        <item>Press a nickel-sized indentation in the center of each patty.</item>
        <item>Heat a large cast-iron skillet over medium-high heat.</item>
        <item>Add sesame oil to pan; swirl to coat.</item>
        <item>Add patties; cook patties for 3 minutes on each side or until desired degree of done.</item>
        <item>Brush tops of patties evenly with hoisin; cook for 30 seconds.</item>
        <item>Place 1 patty on bottom half of each bun; top each patty with 6 cucumber slices and top half of bun.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="pan_bagnat_dir">
        <item>In a small bowl, whisk together the optional anchovies, the garlic, vinegar, mustard, salt and pepper.</item>
        <item>Slowly drizzle in oil, whisking constantly.</item>
        <item>If using a country loaf, pull out some soft interior crumb to form a cavity.</item>
        <item>If using a ciabatta, you won\'t need to eliminate anything.</item>
        <item>If using a Kirby cucumber, slice thinly.</item>
        <item>If using a regular cucumber, peel, halve lengthwise, and scoop out seeds from one half.</item>
        <item>Thinly slice seedless half.</item>
        <item>Add sliced cucumber to vinaigrette and toss well.</item>
        <item>Spread half the cucumbers on bottom of bread.</item>
        <item>Top with tomato and onion slices, then with tuna, basil, olives and egg slices.</item>
        <item>Top egg with remaining cucumbers and vinaigrette.</item>
        <item>Cover with second bread half and firmly press sandwich together.</item>
        <item>Wrap sandwich tightly in foil, waxed paper or plastic wrap, then place in a plastic bag.</item>
        <item>Put sandwich under a weight such as a cast-iron frying pan topped with a filled kettle, or have a child about 7 years old sit on it.</item>
        <item>Weight sandwich for 7 to 10 minutes, then flip and weight it for another 7 to 10 minutes (or as long as you can get the child to sit still).</item>
        <item>Unwrap, slice and serve immediately, or keep it wrapped for up to 8 hours before serving.</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- SPICE -->
    <string-array name="vietnamese_dir">
        <item>With chef\'s knife, mash garlic and salt into a paste.</item>
        <item>Transfer to a mixing bowl and add vinegar and sugar, stirring to dissolve.</item>
        <item>Add carrots, onions and chilies.</item>
        <item>Toss to coat, set aside.</item>
        <item>Slice baguette into 4 equal lengths.</item>
        <item>Split each piece horizontally.</item>
        <item>Spread cut sides with mayonnaise.</item>
        <item>Arrange the meat on the 4 bottom halves.</item>
        <item>Sprinkle with lime juice and 5-spice powder.</item>
        <item>Top with the carrot salad and a shower of cilantro leaves.</item>
        <item>Cover with bread tops.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="spicy_chic_fillet_dir">
        <item>Preheat 6 to 8 cups of oil in a deep fryer to 350 degrees.</item>
        <item>Combine the pepper sauce and water in a small bowl.</item>
        <item>Combine the flour, salt, cayenne pepper, black pepper, onion powder, paprika and garlic powder in another shallow bowl.</item>
        <item>Pound each of the chicken pieces with a mallet until about 3/8-inch thick.</item>
        <item>Trim each breast fillet if necessary to help it fit on the bun.</item>
        <item>Working with one fillet at a time, coat each piece with the flour, then dredge it in the diluted pepper sauce.</item>
        <item>Coat the chicken once again in the flour mixture and set it aside until the rest of the chicken is coated.</item>
        <item>Fry the chicken fillets for 8 to 12 minutes or until they are light brown and crispy.</item>
        <item>Remove the chicken to a rack or to paper towels to drain.</item>
        <item>As chicken is frying, prepare each sandwich by grilling the face of the hamburger buns on a hot skillet over medium heat.</item>
        <item>Spread about 2 teaspoons of mayonnaise on the face of each of the inverted top buns.</item>
        <item>Place a tomato slice onto the mayonnaise, then stack a leaf of lettuce on top of the tomato.</item>
        <item>On each of the bottom buns, stack one piece of chicken.</item>
        <item>Flip the top half of each sandwich onto the bottom half and serve hot.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="spicy_egg_salad_dir">
        <item>Combine chiles, eggs, mayonnaise dressing, green onion and hot pepper sauce in medium bowl.</item>
        <item>Season with salt and ground black pepper.</item>
        <item>Spread egg salad on toasted bagels or English muffins or bread.</item>
        <item>Simple right.</item>
        <item>Have Fun.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="roast_beef_avocado_dir">
        <item>Combine mayo, Tabasco, and cilantro in a small bowl.</item>
        <item>Spread mayo mixture on both sides of bread.</item>
        <item>Layer roast beef, cheese, lettuce, and avocado, sprinkle lightly with salt.</item>
        <item>Lightly press on top layer of bread.</item>
        <item>If using large loaf, cut into portions, and serve.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="mint_chutney_dir">
        <item>Finely chop the mint and coriander leaves.</item>
        <item>Transfer to a mixer along with green chillies, garlic, ginger, sugar, lemon juice and some salt.</item>
        <item>Blend well until smooth.</item>
        <item>Add salt if needed and transfer to a bowl.</item>
        <item>Place the bread slices on a flat surface.</item>
        <item>Spread 1 slice with butter and other slice with the chutney.</item>
        <item>Top up with cucumber and tomato slices and cover.</item>
        <item>Cut into squares or triangles or halves.</item>
        <item>Serve at once.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="torta_ahogada_dir">
        <item>Combine chiles, vinegar, pumpkin and sesame seeds, oregano, salt, cumin, allspice, cloves, and garlic in a blender.</item>
        <item>Puree until very smooth.</item>
        <item>Pour through a medium strainer into a bowl, discard solids, and stir in 3⁄4 cup water.</item>
        <item>Heat oven to 350°.</item>
        <item>Split roll and fill bottom half with pork.</item>
        <item>Place on baking sheet and bake until warmed through and bread is toasted, about 6 minutes.</item>
        <item>Add onion, radish, and top bun.</item>
        <item>Pour chile de arbol sauce over sandwich, and let sit, so that the sauce soaks in.</item>
        <item>Serve</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="austrian_bosna_dir">
        <item>Grill sausages (a George Foreman Grill works great for this).</item>
        <item>Meanwhile, prepare the buns by cutting them open and spreading one side with curry ketchup and the other with Dijon mustard.</item>
        <item>When the sausage is cooked through, put two in each bun and grill on a panini grill, Foreman grill, or in a skillet with heavy cans placed on top of the buns.</item>
        <item>When bread is nicely toasted and flattened, remove from grill and generously sprinkle the sausages with curry powder and onion.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="deviled_ham_dir">
        <item>Place ham and onion into a food processor and process until very finely chopped.</item>
        <item>Transfer ham mixture to a bowl.</item>
        <item>Thoroughly mix in salad dressing, honey, prepared mustard, Worcestershire sauce, dry mustard powder, hot pepper sauce, paprika, salt, and white pepper.</item>
        <item>Refrigerate ham spread covered until ready to use.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="pulled_pork_dir">
        <item>Preheat oven to 250 degrees F (120 degrees C).</item>
        <item>Mix brown sugar, paprika, garlic powder, black pepper, and salt in a bowl.</item>
        <item>Spread mustard over pork roast and sprinkle with brown sugar mixture, using the entire amount.</item>
        <item>Line a shallow baking dish with aluminum foil.</item>
        <item>Place a rack in the prepared baking dish and arrange pork roast on rack.</item>
        <item>Bake in the preheated oven until very tender, 9 to 11 hours.</item>
        <item>Let pork cool, then shred into bite-size pieces.</item>
        <item>Stir barbecue sauce into pork to moisten.</item>
        <item>Serve with hamburger buns.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="banh_mi_dir">
        <item>Place rice vinegar, water, and sugar into a saucepan over medium heat, bring to a boil, and stir until the sugar has dissolved, about 1 minute.</item>
        <item>Allow the mixture to cool.</item>
        <item>Pour the cooled vinegar mixture over the carrot, radish, and onion in a bowl, and allow to stand for at least 30 minutes.</item>
        <item>Drain off the excess vinegar mixture after the vegetables have marinated.</item>
        <item>While the vegetables are marinating, preheat the oven\'s broiler, and set the oven rack about 6 inches from the heat source.</item>
        <item>Lightly oil a slotted broiler pan.</item>
        <item>Sprinkle the chicken breast with garlic salt and pepper, and broil on slotted broiler pan, turning once, until the center of the chicken breast is no longer pink and the surface has browned, about 6 minutes per side.</item>
        <item>Remove the broiled chicken, and slice into bite-size pieces.</item>
        <item>Slice the baguette in half the long way, and pull the center of the bread out of the baguette halves, leaving a cavity for the filling.</item>
        <item>Place the baguette halves under the broiler to lightly toast, 2 to 3 minutes.</item>
        <item>To assemble the bahn mi sandwich, spread each half of the toasted baguette with mayonnaise.</item>
        <item>Fill the cavity of the bottom half of the bread with broiled chicken, cucumber slices, pickled carrot, onion, and radish, cilantro leaves, and jalapeno pepper.</item>
        <item>Squeeze a wedge of lime over the filling, and top with the other half of the baguette.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="the_dagwood_dir">
        <item>Layout the 3 bread slices.</item>
        <item>On first slice spread mayonnaise, layer cucumber slices, cheddar cheese, &#189; of the lettuce, 1 tomato slice, ham and top with mustard spread.</item>
        <item>Add second piece of bread on top.</item>
        <item>Spread horseradish and relish.</item>
        <item>Layer onion, second tomato slice, swiss cheese, second half of the lettuce and turkey.</item>
        <item>Add third piece of bread (spread bottom with mayonnaise if desired).</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="katsu_sando_dir">
        <item>Lightly season both sides of the pork chops with salt and pepper and sprinkle with flour.</item>
        <item>Dip the chops into the lightly beaten egg and then into the panko, making sure that all sides are coated.</item>
        <item>Heat up half an inch of oil in a large frying pan over medium high heat.</item>
        <item>Fry the chops until golden brown and cooked through, flipping once, about 2 minutes per side.</item>
        <item>Drain on paper towels.</item>
        <item>Toast the bread and spread Kewpie mayo on one slice and Japanese mustard on the other.</item>
        <item>Drizzle the bread or chops with the tonkatsu sauce, place on a slice of bread and top with the other slice.</item>
        <item>Slice off the crusts, if desired and enjoy immediately.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="chicken_shawarma_dir">
        <item>Preheat grill to medium-high heat.</item>
        <item>To prepare chicken, combine first 6 ingredients in a medium bowl.</item>
        <item>Add chicken to bowl; toss well to coat.</item>
        <item>Let stand at room temperature 20 minutes.</item>
        <item>To prepare sauce, combine yogurt and next 4 ingredients (through 1 garlic clove), stirring with a whisk.</item>
        <item>Thread 2 chicken strips onto each of 8 (12-inch) skewers.</item>
        <item>Place kebabs on a grill rack coated with cooking spray; grill 4 minutes on each side or until done.</item>
        <item>Place pitas on grill rack; grill 1 minute on each side or until lightly toasted.</item>
        <item>Place 1 pita on each of 4 plates; top each serving with &#188; cup lettuce and 2 tomato slices.</item>
        <item>Top each serving with 4 chicken pieces; drizzle each serving with 2 tablespoons sauce.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="roti_john_dir">
        <item>Cut the bread into thick slices.</item>
        <item>In a wide shallow bowl, mix the eggs, onion and corned beef.</item>
        <item>Season with salt and pepper to taste.</item>
        <item>Heat about 2 tablespoons oil in a frying pan.</item>
        <item>Dip one side of each slice of bread into the egg mixture and gently place egg-side down into the pan.</item>
        <item>Repeat with as many slices as will fit.</item>
        <item>Press down with a spatula.</item>
        <item>When browned, flip to brown the other side.</item>
        <item>Remove and drain on paper towels.</item>
        <item>Repeat until all the bread or egg mixture is finished.</item>
        <item>Serve hot.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ham_cheese_dir">
        <item>Preheat oven to 350 degrees F (175 degrees C).</item>
        <item>In a medium bowl, mix together butter, poppy seeds, onion, Worcestershire sauce and prepared Dijon-style mustard.</item>
        <item>Slice rolls in half horizontally and set aside tops.</item>
        <item>Spread bottoms with the butter mixture.</item>
        <item>Top with ham and Swiss cheese.</item>
        <item>Replace tops.</item>
        <item>Arrange rolls in a single layer in a medium baking dish.</item>
        <item>Bake in the preheated oven 10 to 12 minutes, until rolls are lightly browned and cheese is melted.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="oyster_roll_dir">
        <item>Whisk together mayonnaise, chipotle, and lemon juice and chill mixture, its surface covered with plastic wrap.</item>
        <item>Heat oil in a deep heavy pot over high heat until it registers 375°F on deep-fat thermometer, about 12 minutes.</item>
        <item>While oil is heating, whisk together egg, milk, and 1 teaspoon salt in a bowl.</item>
        <item>Shake cornmeal, remaining 1 &#189; teaspoons salt, and pepper in a plastic or paper bag until combined well.</item>
        <item>Working in batches, add oysters to egg mixture, then lift out, letting excess drip off, and transfer to cornmeal in bag, shaking to coat well.</item>
        <item>Carefully transfer to oil, knocking off excess coating, and fry, turning occasionally, until golden and just cooked through, 1 to 2 minutes.</item>
        <item>Transfer with a slotted spoon to paper towels to drain.</item>
        <item>Coat and fry remaining oysters in same manner, returning oil to 375°F for each batch.</item>
        <item>Halve loaf crosswise and horizontally, cutting all the way through, and spread one cut side of each piece with mayonnaise.</item>
        <item>Sandwich oysters and lettuce between bread, pressing gently.</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- SWEET -->

    <string-array name="cara_choco_ban_dir">
        <item>Mix butter and brown sugar in small bowl to blend.</item>
        <item>Spread over 1 side of all four bread slices.</item>
        <item>Place 2 slices, buttered side down, on plate.</item>
        <item>Skewer 4 marshmallows each on two metal skewers.</item>
        <item>Hold skewers over open flame and toast until marshmallows are blackened in spots, about 10 seconds.</item>
        <item>Divide marshmallows between bread slices on plate, leaving 1 inch border.</item>
        <item>Sprinkle chocolate chips over marshmallows, dividing equally.</item>
        <item>Top with banana slices.</item>
        <item>Cover with remaining bread, buttered side up, pressing slightly.</item>
        <item>Heat large nonstick skillet over medium-high heat.</item>
        <item>Add sandwiches; cook until brown, about 1 &#189; minutes per side.</item>
        <item>Transfer sandwiches to work surface.</item>
        <item>Cool 1 minute.</item>
        <item>Cut diagonally in half and serve.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="choco_oat_moon_dir">
        <item>Arrange racks in upper and lower thirds of oven; preheat to 350°F.</item>
        <item>Line 3 baking sheets with parchment paper.</item>
        <item>Whisk flour, baking powder, baking soda, and salt in a medium bowl.</item>
        <item>Combine oats, cherries, pecans, and chocolate in a large bowl.</item>
        <item>Using an electric mixer, beat butter and sugar in another large bowl, occasionally scraping down sides of bowl, until smooth, about 2 minutes.</item>
        <item>Add egg and vanilla and beat to blend. Scrape down sides of bowl.</item>
        <item>With machine running at low speed, gradually add flour mixture; beat just to blend.</item>
        <item>Stir in oat mixture with a wooden spoon just to blend.</item>
        <item>Using a 1-ounce ice cream scoop or scooping out 2 level tablespoonfuls of dough, measure dough into 36 portions.</item>
        <item>Divide among baking sheets. Using your hands, gently press down on each dough ball until &#189;" thick.</item>
        <item>Bake cookies for 12 minutes.</item>
        <item>Rotate sheets front to back and top to bottom.</item>
        <item>Continue baking until cookies are golden brown and edges have begun to set but centers are still soft (cookies will appear underdone and shiny in centers), 7 to 8 minutes longer.</item>
        <item>Do not overbake.</item>
        <item>Let cookies cool on baking sheets.</item>
        <item>DO AHEAD: Cookies can be made 2 days ahead. Store airtight at room temperature.</item>
        <item>Spread 1 tablespoon marshmallow creme on bottom of 18 cookies.</item>
        <item>Sandwich with remaining cookies.</item>
        <item>Place chocolate and honey in a medium bowl.</item>
        <item>Bring cream just to a boil in a small saucepan.</item>
        <item>Pour over chocolate and honey; let stand for 1 minute; stir until melted and smooth.</item>
        <item>Drizzle over cookies or serve alongside sandwich cookies for dipping.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="blue_choco_panini_dir">
        <item>Preheat your panini press, grill pan, or griddle.</item>
        <item>Spread 4 slices of bread with softened butter on all sides.</item>
        <item>Cut each marshmallow into three pieces and arrange three each on two of the slices of buttered bread (sticky-side down makes this easiest!).</item>
        <item>Top with white chocolate and blueberries, then cover with remaining two slices of bread to make two sandwiches.</item>
        <item>Gently place each sandwich on the preheated grill and either close the panini maker, or top with a heavy object such as another heavy pan, a heavy heat-proof plate, or a tea kettle filled with water.</item>
        <item>Press down and let grill about 1 &#189; to 2 minutes, then flip and cook on other side (if you\'re using a panini press, there is no need to flip.)</item>
        <item>Cut each sandwich in half and sprinkle with a bit of sea salt.</item>
        <item>Serve immediately.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="french_macroons_dir">
        <item>Line 2 large baking sheets with parchment.</item>
        <item>Sift powdered sugar, almond flour, and hazelnut flour (if using) into large bowl.</item>
        <item>Using electric mixer, beat egg whites, sugar, and pinch of salt in medium bowl until medium peaks form.</item>
        <item>Add egg white mixture to almond mixture; fold to incorporate.</item>
        <item>Working in 2 batches, fill pastry bag fitted with &#188;-inch-diameter plain pastry tip with batter.</item>
        <item>Pipe batter in 11/4-inch rounds on baking sheets, spacing 1 inch apart.</item>
        <item>Let rest on sheets at room temperature 20 minutes.</item>
        <item>Position 1 rack in top third and 1 rack in bottom third of oven; preheat to 375°F.</item>
        <item>Bake cookies 5 minutes. Reduce oven temperature to 325°F.</item>
        <item>Continue to bake cookies until puffed and golden on top, about 10 minutes, reversing sheets after 5 minutes.</item>
        <item>Cool cookies on sheets on rack.</item>
        <item>Carefully peel cookies from parchment.</item>
        <item>DO AHEAD Can be made 1 day ahead.</item>
        <item>Store in airtight container at room temperature.</item>
        <item>Stir sugar, honey, 3 tablespoons water, and &#188; teaspoon salt in large saucepan over medium-low heat until sugar dissolves.</item>
        <item>Increase heat to high and boil without stirring until syrup is dark amber, occasionally brushing down sides of pan with wet pastry brush and swirling pan, about 8 minutes.</item>
        <item>Remove from heat and immediately add cream and butter (mixture will bubble vigorously).</item>
        <item>Return pan to stovetop. Attach candy thermometer to side of pan.</item>
        <item>Boil caramel over medium-high heat until candy thermometer registers 234°F, 8 to 10 minutes.</item>
        <item>Transfer caramel filling to medium bowl; cool to room temperature.</item>
        <item>Line rimmed baking sheet with parchment paper.</item>
        <item>Spoon 1 teaspoon caramel filling onto bottom (flat side) of 1 macaroon.</item>
        <item>Top with second macaroon, flat-side down, pressing slightly to adhere and gently pressing filling almost to edge of macaroon.</item>
        <item>Place on prepared sheet. Repeat with remaining filling and macaroons.</item>
        <item>Cover and refrigerate overnight.</item>
        <item>DO AHEAD Can be made 2 days ahead. Store in airtight container in refrigerator.</item>
        <item>Let macaroons stand at room temperature 30 minutes before serving.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="brownie_ice_cream_dir">
        <item>Preheat oven to 350°.</item>
        <item>Cut aluminum foil or parchment paper long enough to fit bottoms of 2 (8-inch) square pans, allowing a 2-inch overhang on each end.</item>
        <item>Lightly coat foil with cooking spray.</item>
        <item>Simmer chocolate and butter together in a small saucepan over low heat until melted.</item>
        <item>Cool slightly.</item>
        <item>Beat sugar and eggs at medium speed with an electric mixer 5 minutes or until light and fluffy.</item>
        <item>Gradually add melted chocolate mixture, beating until blended.</item>
        <item>Stir in vanilla. Fold in flour and salt until blended.</item>
        <item>Divide batter evenly among prepared pans.</item>
        <item>Bake at 350° for 13 to 15 minutes or until a tester inserted in center comes out clean.</item>
        <item>Cool brownies completely in pans on a wire rack; freeze in pans for 2 hours.</item>
        <item>Spread 3 cups ice cream over 1 brownie layer in pan.</item>
        <item>Remove other brownie layer, and peel away foil; place over ice-cream layer, and press gently.</item>
        <item>Cover and freeze until firm, about 4 hours or overnight.</item>
        <item>Remove from pan, remove foil, and cut into quarters.</item>
        <item>Cut each quarter diagonally to form 8 triangles.</item>
        <item>If desired, place chocolate chips into 2 small zip-top plastic bags; seal.</item>
        <item>Microwave 30 seconds at a time until chocolate melts.</item>
        <item>Snip a tiny corner from 1 side of bag; drizzle melted chocolate over bars.</item>
        <item>Serve immediately.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="frozen_yogurt_dir">
        <item>To make cookies: Preheat oven to 300 °F.</item>
        <item>Coat 2 baking sheets with cooking spray.</item>
        <item>Whisk together sugar, oil, milk, egg white and vanilla in a mixing bowl until no lumps of brown sugar remain.</item>
        <item>Add oats, flour, baking soda and cinnamon to the bowl and stir until no traces of dry ingredients remain.</item>
        <item>Divide the dough into 16 equal pieces and form each piece into a ball.</item>
        <item>Place 8 balls on each prepared baking sheet.</item>
        <item>Cover each baking sheet with a piece of plastic wrap or wax paper.</item>
        <item>Firmly press each of the balls into a thin 3-inch circle, using a flat-bottomed cup or bowl.</item>
        <item>Bake the cookies, one sheet at a time, until well-browned, 8 to 10 minutes.</item>
        <item>Transfer to a wire rack to cool completely.</item>
        <item>To make sandwiches: If the pieces of fruit are large, coarsely chop them.</item>
        <item>Soften frozen yogurt in the microwave at medium-low power for 30 to 60 seconds or at room temperature for 10 to 20 minutes; place in a mixing bowl.</item>
        <item>Swirl the fruit into the softened frozen yogurt.</item>
        <item>If the yogurt has become too soft, return it to the freezer to firm up slightly.</item>
        <item>Scoop about &#8531; cup of frozen yogurt onto a cookie and gently press a second cookie on top.</item>
        <item>Repeat with the remaining cookies and frozen yogurt.</item>
        <item>Return the sandwiches to the freezer to firm up.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ice_cream_dir">
        <item>Preheat oven to 350 degrees F (175 degrees C). Lightly grease baking sheets.</item>
        <item>In a large bowl, mix together the cake mix, butter, vanilla extract, eggs, chocolate chips, and butterscotch chips.</item>
        <item>Roll dough into 2-inch balls and place them onto the prepared baking sheets.</item>
        <item>Bake for 10 minutes in the preheated oven.</item>
        <item>Do not over-bake; the cookies should be set, but still soft.</item>
        <item>Let cool on the baking sheet for a few minutes before removing to finish cooling on wire racks.</item>
        <item>Using an ice cream scoop, mold the softened ice cream into a ball about the size of the cookies.</item>
        <item>Place scoop of ice cream between two cookies and gently press together.</item>
        <item>If you like a smooth edge, run the back of a spoon around the edge of the ice cream sandwich.</item>
        <item>Working quickly, fill all of the cookies, lay out on a baking sheet, and place in the freezer to harden.</item>
        <item>Serve when the ice cream has frozen solid.</item>
        <item>Sandwich cookies can be stored in a freezer bag for up to two weeks.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="banana_nutella_dir">
        <item>Spread one tablespoon of Nutella on the face of each slice of bread.</item>
        <item>Top one with banana slices and place second slice on top.</item>
        <item>Heat the frying pan and melt &#189; of the butter.</item>
        <item>Place the sandwich into the pan and fry until golden.</item>
        <item>Add the remaining butter to the pan and flip the sandwich, cooking until the other side is golden.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="japanese_fruit_dir">
        <item>Whip the cream, gradually adding the sugar.</item>
        <item>When you have a soft peak, add the vanilla and continue to whip until you get a stiff peak.</item>
        <item>Spread a few Tbsp of whipped cream on one side of each slice of bread.</item>
        <item>Place a mix of fruit pieces in a single layer, evenly on 4 of the 8 pieces.</item>
        <item>Top the fruit with another slice of bread, cream side down.</item>
        <item>Carefully use the serrated knife to cut the crusts off.</item>
        <item>It is easiest to cut in one direction to minimize the cream from oozing out.</item>
        <item>Cut each sandwich in half (for a personal size) or in quarters (for tea sandwiches).</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="fluffer_nutter_dir">
        <item>Butter 1 side of each slice of bread.</item>
        <item>Coat 1 side of 1 slice of bread with peanut butter.</item>
        <item>Coat 1 side of other slice of bread with Nutella.</item>
        <item>Spread marshmallow fluff between two slices of bread.</item>
        <item>Grill in oiled skillet until toasted and inside of sandwich is gooey and delicious.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="peanut_jelly_dir">
        <item>Heat griddle or skillet to 350 degrees F (175 degrees C).</item>
        <item>Spread butter on one side of each slice of bread.</item>
        <item>Spread peanut butter on unbuttered side of one slice of bread, and jelly on the other.</item>
        <item>Place one slice, buttered side down on the griddle.</item>
        <item>Top with other slice, so that peanut butter and jelly are in the middle.</item>
        <item>Cook for 4 minutes on each side, or until golden brown, and heated through.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="prosciutto_fig_dir">
        <item>Spread 1 teaspoon mustard over 4 bread slices.</item>
        <item>Arrange &#188; cup arugula over each bread slice.</item>
        <item>Divide prosciutto evenly over bread slices; top evenly with cheese and fig slices.</item>
        <item>Spread 1 &#189; teaspoons jam over remaining 4 bread slices.</item>
        <item>Top each serving with 1 bread slice, jam side down.</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="cinnamon_toast_dir">
        <item>In a small bowl, combine butter, sugar and cinnamon and set aside.</item>
        <item>Toast both slices of bread, then remove from toaster.</item>
        <item>While still hot, spread butter mixture over both slices, sprinkle with a little extra sugar and eat immediately.</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- GUILTY -->
    <string-array name="simple_tuna_melt_dir">
        <item>Preheat the oven to 375 degrees F (190 degrees C).</item>
        <item>Place bread slices in the oven to toast while it preheats, and while you make the tuna salad.</item>
        <item>In a small bowl, mix together the tuna, mayonnaise, salt, balsamic vinegar, mustard and dill pickle until well blended.</item>
        <item>Remove bread from the oven, and pile the tuna mixture onto one slice.</item>
        <item>Sprinkle cheese over the other slice of bread.</item>
        <item>Bake for 7 minutes in the preheated oven, or until cheese is melted and tuna is heated through.</item>
        <item>Place the cheese side of the sandwich on top of the tuna side.</item>
        <item>Cut in half and serve immediately.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="potato_chip_dir">
        <item>Spread the mayo on the bread.</item>
        <item>Place the meat, cheese, pickle, onion if using, tomato and chips onto one slice of bread and top it off with the second slice of bread.</item>
        <item>Smash it down a bit and hang on! It gets a bit messy!</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="yakisoba_pan_dir">
        <item>Lightly loosen Yakisoba noodles and set aside.</item>
        <item>Heat vegetable oil in medium skillet on medium heat.</item>
        <item>Add hot dogs, onion, carrot to the skillet and stir-fry for about 5 to 7 minutes or until onions and carrots brown slightly and soften but still have a bite to them.</item>
        <item>Add the cabbage to the skillet and stir-fry for another 3 to 4 minutes.</item>
        <item>Add salt and freshly ground black pepper.</item>
        <item>Add the noodles to the skillet.</item>
        <item>Pour &#188; cup of water or sake over the noodle mixture and cover the skillet.</item>
        <item>Turn down the heat to low and steam for about two minutes.</item>
        <item>Remove the lid to let the remaining liquid evaporate, about 2 minutes.</item>
        <item>Add the Yakisoba sauce. (adjust the amount of sauce to your taste)</item>
        <item>Stir-fry the noodles quickly so the sauce is mixed evenly. Shut off the heat.</item>
        <item>Fill each hot dog bun with Yakisoba, sprinkle with Aonori and top with the pickled ginger and serve.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="fracesinha_dir">
        <item>Make the sauce first by dissolving the cornstarch into the milk.</item>
        <item>Add all the other sauce ingredients and blend in food processor.</item>
        <item>Put it into a pan over low heat and add the bay leaf .</item>
        <item>Stir it until it starts to boil, remove bay leaf and then set aside.</item>
        <item>Assemble the sandwich saving 2 slices of cheese.</item>
        <item>Put the sandwich on a plate or shallow bowl and place the 2 slices of cheese on top.</item>
        <item>Pour the sauce over the sandwich (should be hot, so the cheese melts).</item>
        <item>Eat &#8212; you may want a bib.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="roasted_turkey_dir">
        <item>In small bowl, mix mayonnaise, basil and garlic powder.</item>
        <item>Spread on one side of each bread slice.</item>
        <item>Layer spinach, turkey and bell peppers on 4 slices of bread.</item>
        <item>Top with remaining bread.</item>
        <item>Savour</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="mexican_telera_dir">
        <item>Preheat oven to 350 degrees F.</item>
        <item>Place the mayonnaise and chipotle chiles in a food processor and blend until smooth.</item>
        <item>Generously spread the cut sides of the rolls with the chipotle mayonnaise.</item>
        <item>Cover the bottom half of each roll with 1 thinly sliced chicken breast, overlapping the slices.</item>
        <item>Top each portion of chicken with 5 slices of tomato and 4 slices of avocado.</item>
        <item>Cover with 2 slices of cheese.</item>
        <item>Place assembled sandwiches open faced on a sheet pan and bake until cheese is melted, about 8 minutes.</item>
        <item>Cover the sandwiches, slice in half and serve immediately.</item>
        <item>FOR GRILLED CHICKEN BELOW</item>
        <item>In a large bowl, whisk together the lemon juice, garlic, salt, and paprika.</item>
        <item>While whisking, drizzle in the oil until incorporated.</item>
        <item>Add the chicken, cover, and marinate in the refrigerator for at least 8 hours and up to overnight.</item>
        <item>Preheat a stovetop grill pan until hot.</item>
        <item>Grill the chicken, turning once, until well marked and cooked through, about 15 to 20 minutes.</item>
        <item>When cool enough to handle, slice very thin and make the sandwiches.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="easy_slow_french_dir">
        <item>Trim excess fat from the rump roast, and place in a slow cooker.</item>
        <item>Add the beef broth, onion soup and beer.</item>
        <item>Cook on Low setting for 7 hours.</item>
        <item>Preheat oven to 350 degrees F (175 degrees C).</item>
        <item>Split French rolls, and spread with butter.</item>
        <item>Bake 10 minutes, or until heated through.</item>
        <item>Slice the meat on the diagonal, and place on the rolls.</item>
        <item>Serve the sauce for dipping.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="porchetta_sandwich_dir">
        <item>Combine the ingredients for the salt rub in a small bowl.</item>
        <item>Lightly sprinkle the inside of the pork belly with half of salt rub (you won’t need to use all of it).</item>
        <item>Sprinkle the herb rub and place the tenderloin in the centre of the belly.</item>
        <item>Tightly roll up the belly around the tenderloin and tie together with kitchen twine.</item>
        <item>Rub the skin generously with oil and the rest of the salt rub.</item>
        <item>Place your porchetta in a dish, cover and place in the fridge for at least 12 hours.</item>
        <item>Heat the oven to 275°F.</item>
        <item>Place the porchetta on a rack in a deep roasting pan.</item>
        <item>Lots of fat will be rendered out of the porchetta, so make sure your roasting pan is deep enough.</item>
        <item>Roast on the centre rack of the oven for 4 hours.</item>
        <item>Use a meat thermometer to check that the internal temperature is 160°F.</item>
        <item>Blast the heat up to 450°F and continue to roast for 35 minutes, keeping an eye on the skin.</item>
        <item>You want the crackling golden brown and crispy, not burnt.</item>
        <item>Remove from the oven, let rest for 15 to 20 minutes, slice and enjoy!</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="chicken_biscuit_dir">
        <item>Preheat oven to 400°F.</item>
        <item>Slice the chicken breasts in half lengthwise, then half again horizontally to create 8 thin, triangle-shaped pieces of chicken.</item>
        <item>In a small bowl, stir together the flour and spices.</item>
        <item>In a second small bowl, whisk together the egg and milk.</item>
        <item>Heat oil in a large skillet on top of a medium-hot stove.</item>
        <item>Open the flaky layered biscuits and place them on a baking sheet.</item>
        <item>Bake in preheated oven for 12 to 14 minutes, or until golden brown.</item>
        <item>While your biscuits are baking, dip the chicken pieces into the egg and milk mixture, then into the spiced flour mixture.</item>
        <item>Fry in the hot oil.</item>
        <item>Whisk together the melted butter and honey.</item>
        <item>Remove the biscuits from the oven and use a basting brush to spread melted honey butter on top of the biscuits.</item>
        <item>Slice each biscuit in half, then place a piece of cooked chicken in the center.</item>
        <item>Serve with orange juice and enjoy!</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="meat_loaf_dir">
        <item>Spread 1 slice of bread with mustard.</item>
        <item>Spread the other slice of bread with ketchup.</item>
        <item>Brown meat loaf slice on both sides in 1 teaspoon of olive oil in skillet or on griddle until heated through.</item>
        <item>Put browned meatloaf slice on the mustard-smeared bread.</item>
        <item>Put a slice of cheese on top of the meat loaf.</item>
        <item>Cover with the ketchup-smeared bread.</item>
        <item>Heat remaining 1 teaspoon olive oil in skillet or on griddle.</item>
        <item>Grill the sandwich over medium heat on both sides, until golden.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="cemitas_mexican_dir">
        <item>Slice the rolls sandwich style, then toast or grill the cut sides until browned.</item>
        <item>Divide the meat between each of the 4 bottoms of the rolls.</item>
        <item>Top with cheese, avocado slices, onion and cilantro (or papalo) leaves.</item>
        <item>Lay as much or as little of the chipotle strips on top.</item>
        <item>You may also brush a bit of the extra adobo sauce onto the inside of the top of the rolls before closing the sandwich.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="the_falafel_dir">
        <item>Place the dried chickpeas and baking soda in a large bowl filled with water to cover the chicpeas by at least 2 inches.</item>
        <item>Soak overnight for 16 to 18 hours.</item>
        <item>When ready, drain the chickpeas completely and pat them dry.</item>
        <item>Place the fresh leaves of parsley, cilantro and dill in a large food processor.</item>
        <item>Pulse to finely chop the herbs.</item>
        <item>Now add the chickpeas, garlic and spices.</item>
        <item>Run the food processor 40 seconds at a time until all is well combined forming a smooth falafel mixture.</item>
        <item>Transfer the falafel mixture into a container and cover tightly.</item>
        <item>Refrigerate for at least 1 hour or until ready to fry (up to one whole night).</item>
        <item>Just before frying, add the baking powder and sesame seeds to the falafel mixture and stir with a spoon.</item>
        <item>Scoop tablespoonfuls of the falafel mixture and form into patties (&#189; inch in thickness each).</item>
        <item>Fill a medium saucepan 3 inches up with oil. Heat the oil on medium-high until it bubbles softly.</item>
        <item>Carefully drop the falafel patties in the oil, let them fry for about 3 to 4 minutes or so until medium brown.</item>
        <item>Avoid crowding the falafel in the saucepan, fry them in batches if necessary.</item>
        <item>Place the fried falafel patties in a colander or plate lined with paper towels to drain.</item>
        <item>Assemble the falafel patties in pita bread with hummus, arugula, tomato and cucumbers. Enjoy!</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="the_primanti_dir">
        <item>Make the slaw by mixing together the cabbage, 2 tablespoons of vegetable oil, the vinegar, sugar, adobo seasoning, and black pepper until thoroughly combined.</item>
        <item>Cover and refrigerate.</item>
        <item>Heat oil in a deep-fryer or large saucepan to 375 degrees F (190 degrees C).</item>
        <item>Cut the potatoes into &#188; inch thick fries, and fry until they float and are golden brown, 4 to 5 minutes. Set the fries aside.</item>
        <item>Preheat oven to 225 degrees F (110 degrees C).</item>
        <item>Place the bread on a baking sheet, and toast to a light brown in the preheated oven, 3 to 5 minutes.</item>
        <item>Remove half the bread slices.</item>
        <item>Place &#188; of the pastrami on the remaining 4 bread slices, and top with provolone cheese.</item>
        <item>Return to the oven until the pastrami is hot and the cheese is melted, about 5 more minutes.</item>
        <item>To assemble, top the melted cheese of each sandwich with French fries, cole slaw, 2 tomato slices, and the top pieces of bread.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="peanut_chicken_pitas_dir">
        <item>Combine the first 5 ingredients, tossing well to coat.</item>
        <item>Stir in chile paste, if desired.</item>
        <item>Fill each pita half with about &#189; cup chicken mixture, &#188; cup bean sprouts, 1 tablespoon carrot and 1 tablespoon cilantro.</item>
        <item>Savour the dark meat.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="italian_beef_sandwich_dir">
        <item>Combine water with salt, ground black pepper, oregano, basil, onion salt, parsley, garlic powder, bay leaf and salad dressing mix in a saucepan.</item>
        <item>Stir well, and bring to a boil.</item>
        <item>Place roast in slow cooker, and pour salad dressing mixture over the meat.</item>
        <item>Cover, and cook on Low for 10 to 12 hours, or on High for 4 to 5 hours.</item>
        <item>When done, remove bay leaf, and shred meat with a fork.</item>
        <item>Assemble the meat between the italian breads and enjoy.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="sloppy_joe_dir">
        <item>Heat oil in a large pot. Saute onions 3 minutes until tender.</item>
        <item>Add ground beef to pot. Cook until brown, stirring to separate meat. Drain well.</item>
        <item>Stir in BBQ sauce (or Ketchup), mustard and Worcestershire.</item>
        <item>Simmer about 5 minutes until flavors are blended.</item>
        <item>Spoon onto slider rolls.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="gatsby_sandwich_dir">
        <item> Heat the olive oil in a heavy skillet over medium-high heat.</item>
        <item>Add the bologna in a single layer and cook until undersides are browned, 2–3 minutes.</item>
        <item>Flip and continue to cook until browned, about 2 minutes more.</item>
        <item>While the bologna cooks, stir together some ketchup and hot sauce, to taste.</item>
        <item>Remove the griddled bologna from the heat and arrange inside the toasted roll.</item>
        <item>Top the meat with the hot French fries, then with the spicy ketchup.</item>
        <item>Finish with the shredded lettuce and close the sandwich.</item>
        <item>Serve immediately.</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--=================VEGGIE=======================-->

    <string-array name="grilled_zucchini_dir">
        <item>Heat a large grill pan over medium-high heat.</item>
        <item>Place zucchini in a shallow dish.</item>
        <item>Add 2 teaspoons oil and garlic; toss to coat.</item>
        <item>Arrange zucchini in grill pan; cook 2 minutes on each side or until grill marks appear.</item>
        <item>Cut each zucchini piece in half crosswise.</item>
        <item>Return zucchini to shallow dish.</item>
        <item>Drizzle with vinegar.</item>
        <item>Sprinkle with salt and black pepper.</item>
        <item>Brush bottom halves of rolls with the remaining 2 teaspoons oil.</item>
        <item>Top evenly with zucchini, basil, tomatoes, and mozzarella.</item>
        <item>Brush cut side of roll tops with remaining liquid from shallow dish, and place on sandwiches.</item>
        <item>Heat the sandwiches in pan until warm.</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="caesar_salad_dir">
        <item>Spread dressing evenly on cut sides of bagels.</item>
        <item>Sprinkle with pepper.</item>
        <item>Arrange half of red onion, romaine lettuce, and cheese on bottom halves of bagels, and repeat layers.</item>
        <item>Top with the top halves of bagels.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="roasted_red_dir">
        <item>Spread cucumber and bell peppers onto several layers of heavy-duty paper towels.</item>
        <item>Let stand 5 minutes to drain excess moisture.</item>
        <item>Scrape into a medium bowl using a rubber spatula.</item>
        <item>Add the cheeses, onion, salt, and garlic.</item>
        <item>Stir with a fork until well blended.</item>
        <item>Spread about &#189; cup cheese mixture over 4 bread slices.</item>
        <item>Top each serving with 2 lettuce leaves and 1 bread slice.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="feta_basil_dir">
        <item>Combine first 4 ingredients, tossing with a fork until well combined.</item>
        <item>Spread about 2 &#189; tablespoons cheese mixture onto each of 4 bread slices.</item>
        <item>Top each sandwich with 2 tomato slices and 1 bread slice.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="tomato_basil_dir">
        <item>Bring balsamic vinegar to a boil in a small saucepan over medium-high heat.</item>
        <item>Cook until reduced to 3 tablespoons (about 8 minutes).</item>
        <item>While vinegar reduces, brush cut side of top half of bread with oil.</item>
        <item>Top evenly with basil, cheese, and tomatoes.</item>
        <item>Sprinkle evenly with salt and pepper.</item>
        <item>Brush cut side of bottom half of bread with reduced vinegar; place on top of sandwich. Invert sandwich.</item>
        <item>Heat a large grill pan over medium-high heat.</item>
        <item>Coat the pan with cooking spray.</item>
        <item>Add sandwich to pan.</item>
        <item>Place a cast-iron or heavy skillet on top of sandwich, and gently press to flatten.</item>
        <item>Leave skillet on; cook 3 minutes on each side or until cheese melts and bread is toasted.</item>
        <item>Cut sandwich into 4 equal pieces.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="veggie_hummus_dir">
        <item>Heat a large grill pan over medium-high heat.</item>
        <item>Brush onion, bell pepper, and eggplant with 1 tablespoon oil.</item>
        <item>Add onion and bell pepper to pan; cook 3 minutes on each side or until grill marks appear.</item>
        <item>Remove from pan.</item>
        <item>Add eggplant to pan; cook 3 minutes on each side or until grill marks appear.</item>
        <item>Remove from pan; coarsely chop vegetables.</item>
        <item>Combine vegetables, remaining 1 tablespoon oil, parsley, and salt; toss to combine.</item>
        <item>Spread &#188; cup hummus over each flatbread, leaving a &#189; inch border around edges.</item>
        <item>Divide vegetables over each flatbread; top each serving with 2 tablespoons cheese.</item>
        <item>Roll up wraps, and cut diagonally in half.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="open_eggplant_dir">
        <item>Preheat broiler to high.</item>
        <item>Place marinara in a microwave-safe measuring cup.</item>
        <item>Microwave at HIGH for 2 minutes or until hot; keep warm.</item>
        <item>Place flour in a shallow dish. Place eggs in another dish. Place panko in another.</item>
        <item>Sprinkle eggplant evenly with salt.</item>
        <item>Dredge both sides of eggplant slices in flour; dip in egg, and dredge in panko.</item>
        <item>Place breaded eggplant slices on a baking sheet coated with cooking spray.</item>
        <item>Broil eggplant 3 minutes on each side or until lightly browned.</item>
        <item>Transfer eggplant slices to a plate.</item>
        <item>Place bread slices on baking sheet; top each slice with 1 basil leaf.</item>
        <item>Place 1 eggplant slice over each leaf; top eggplant with 1 basil leaf and &#189; ounce cheese.</item>
        <item>Top cheese with remaining slices of eggplant; finish with &#189; ounce of cheese over each eggplant slice.</item>
        <item>Broil eggplant stacks 3 minutes or until cheese is lightly browned and bubbly.</item>
        <item>Spoon 2 tablespoons marinara over each serving.</item>
        <item>Top with remaining basil leaves.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="beet_brown_dir">
        <item>Preheat broiler to high.</item>
        <item>Cut each bread slice into a 3-inch circle using a round cutter.</item>
        <item>Lightly coat bread rounds with cooking spray.</item>
        <item>Arrange bread rounds in a single layer on a baking sheet.</item>
        <item>Broil 2 minutes on each side or until lightly toasted. Cool on a wire rack.</item>
        <item>Reduce oven temperature to 400°.</item>
        <item>Place a baking sheet in oven to preheat.</item>
        <item>Combine rice and next 7 ingredients (through pepper) in a medium bowl.</item>
        <item>Combine mustard and egg, stirring well.</item>
        <item>Add egg mixture to rice mixture; stir until well blended.</item>
        <item>Spoon &#8531; cup rice mixture into a (2 &#189; inch) round cookie cutter; pack mixture down.</item>
        <item>Remove mold. Repeat procedure 7 times to form 8 patties.</item>
        <item>Heat a large skillet over medium-high heat.</item>
        <item>Add 1 tablespoon oil to pan; swirl to coat.</item>
        <item>Carefully add 4 patties to pan; cook 2 minutes.</item>
        <item>Carefully transfer patties to preheated baking sheet, turning patties over and arranging in a single layer.</item>
        <item>Repeat procedure with remaining 1 tablespoon oil and remaining 4 patties.</item>
        <item>Place pan in oven; bake patties at 400° for 9 minutes.</item>
        <item>Top each patty with 1 cheese slice; bake an additional 1 minute or until cheese is soft and patties are set.</item>
        <item>Place 8 toasted bread rounds on a flat surface; top each round with 1 patty.</item>
        <item>Divide watercress evenly among sliders; top with the remaining toasted bread rounds.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="farmers_market_dir">
        <item>Preheat grill to medium-high.</item>
        <item>Brush 1 tablespoon olive oil evenly over both sides of eggplant, onion, and zucchini.</item>
        <item>Sprinkle with rosemary, pepper, and salt.</item>
        <item>Combine 1 tablespoon oil and vinegar in a bowl.</item>
        <item>Brush vinegar mixture over cut sides of bread.</item>
        <item>Place onion on grill rack coated with cooking spray, and grill for 6 minutes on each side or until tender.</item>
        <item>Remove from grill, and separate into rings. Grill eggplant and zucchini 4 minutes on each side or until tender.</item>
        <item>Cut zucchini pieces in half crosswise.</item>
        <item>Place bread, cut sides down, on grill rack; grill 2 minutes. Remove from grill.</item>
        <item>Place 1 piece of cheese on bottom halves bread portions.</item>
        <item>Top each serving with 1 eggplant slice, 1 tomato slice, 1 basil leaf, 2 pieces zucchini, &#188; of onion rings, 1 eggplant slice, 1 tomato slice, 1 basil leaf, 1 piece of cheese and top half of bread.</item>
        <item>Place sandwiches on grill rack; grill 2 minutes, covered, or until cheese melts.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="baked_bean_dir">
        <item>Butter both slices of bread.</item>
        <item>Place one slice buttered side down on the preheated toasted sandwich maker.</item>
        <item>Empty contents of can on to bread.</item>
        <item>Top with cheese.</item>
        <item>Followed by the last piece of bread buttered side up.</item>
        <item>Toast 3 to 4 minutes, or until golden brown.</item>
        <item>Cut into either 2 triangles or 4 triangles.</item>
        <item>Serve.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="cucumber_sand_dir">
        <item>Place cucumber slices between 2 paper towels set in a colander.</item>
        <item>Allow liquid to drain, about 10 minutes.</item>
        <item>Mix cream cheese, mayonnaise, garlic powder, onion salt, and Worcestershire sauce in a bowl until smooth.</item>
        <item>Spread cream cheese mixture evenly on one side of each bread slice.</item>
        <item>Divide cucumber slices over half of the bread slices; sprinkle lemon pepper on cucumber.</item>
        <item>Stack the other half of the bread slices with spread sides down over the cucumber slices to make sandwiches.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="trini_doubles_dir">
        <item>BARA:</item>
        <item>Mix all the ingredients dry in a bowl.</item>
        <item>Add the water and knead until a smooth dough is formed.</item>
        <item>Then add the tablespoon of oil over the dough.</item>
        <item>Cover with a cloth and leave to rest for 1 hour or until double its size.</item>
        <item>Spread a thin layer oil over the surface you're using and make little balls about 2 inches in diameter.</item>
        <item>Heat the oil over a medium to high flame and spread the bara dough with your hands.</item>
        <item>Fry on both sides for 7 to 10 seconds.</item>
        <item>Then drain on paper towels.</item>
        <item>CHANNA:</item>
        <item>Soak the channa overnight and place to boil.</item>
        <item>About 25 minutes later, add the baking soda.</item>
        <item>Continue boiling for about 30 minutes or until soft.</item>
        <item>Heat the oil over a medium flame.</item>
        <item>Mix the curry, geera, and masala in &#188; cup of water and add to the pot.</item>
        <item>Add the onion and garlic; saute until golden and the curry is just about to get dry.</item>
        <item>Add the channa; simmer for 20 minutes.</item>
        <item>Pour enough water to cover the channa.</item>
        <item>When its nearly finished, mash a few of the channa to form a sauce.</item>
        <item>Mix in the finely chopped chadon beni and adjust salt and pepper to taste</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="grilled_spaghetti_dir">
        <item>Melt butter with garlic powder in a large skillet.</item>
        <item>Cut a slice of the crust off the top and bottom of each hoagie roll.</item>
        <item>Brush the cut sides with some of the garlic-flavored butter.</item>
        <item>Split the rolls and line the insides with mozzarella cheese slices.</item>
        <item>Mix spaghetti and spaghetti sauce together in a bowl.</item>
        <item>Divide between the hoagie rolls and sandwich the rolls around the cheese and pasta mixture.</item>
        <item>Grill the sandwiches in the skillet until the cheese melts completely, about 5 minutes per side.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="spinach_feta_dir">
        <item>Mince the garlic and add it to a skillet with the olive oil.</item>
        <item>Cook over medium-low heat for 1 to 2 minutes, or until it begins to soften.</item>
        <item>Add the frozen spinach, turn the heat up to medium, and cook for about 5 minutes, or until heated through and most of the excess moisture has evaporated away.</item>
        <item>Season lightly with salt and pepper.</item>
        <item>Cut the rolls in half.</item>
        <item>Add about &#188; cup of shredded mozzarella and &#189; oz. of feta to the bottom half of each roll.</item>
        <item>Divide the cooked spinach between the two sandwiches, then top with a pinch of red pepper flakes, plus &#188; more shredded mozzarella on each.</item>
        <item>Place the top half of the ciabatta roll on the sandwiches and transfer them to a large non-stick skillet.</item>
        <item>Fill a large pot with a few inches of water to create weight, then place the pot on top of the sandwiches to press them down like a panini press.</item>
        <item>Turn the heat on to medium-low and cook until the sandwiches are crispy on the bottom.</item>
        <item>Carefully flip the sandwiches, place the weighted pot back on top, and cook until crispy on the other side and the cheese is melted.</item>
        <item>Serve warm.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="california_grilled_dir">
        <item>In a bowl, mix the mayonnaise, minced garlic, and lemon juice.</item>
        <item>Set aside in the refrigerator.</item>
        <item>Preheat the grill for high heat.</item>
        <item>Brush vegetables with olive oil on each side.</item>
        <item>Brush grate with oil.</item>
        <item>Place bell peppers and zucchini closest to the middle of the grill, and set onion and squash pieces around them.</item>
        <item>Cook for about 3 minutes, turn, and cook for another 3 minutes.</item>
        <item>The peppers may take a bit longer.</item>
        <item>Remove from grill, and set aside.</item>
        <item>Spread some of the mayonnaise mixture on the cut sides of the bread, and sprinkle each one with feta cheese.</item>
        <item>Place on the grill cheese side up, and cover with lid for 2 to 3 minutes.</item>
        <item>This will warm the bread, and slightly melt the cheese.</item>
        <item>Watch carefully so the bottoms don't burn.</item>
        <item>Remove from grill, and layer with the vegetables.</item>
        <item>Enjoy as open faced grilled sandwiches.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="mushroom_sand_dir">
        <item>Heat a teaspoon of olive oil in a wok or a heavy bottomed pan on medium heat.</item>
        <item>Add the chopped mushrooms and sauté until water has evaporated (mushrooms give out water while being cooked).</item>
        <item>Once all the water and moisture is evaporated, add the green chillies, salt and black pepper and sauté until all the ingredients come together.</item>
        <item>Turn off heat; stir in coriander leaves, mix and set aside.</item>
        <item>You need 2 slices of bread to make 1 sandwich.</item>
        <item>Spread the butter on the slices of bread.</item>
        <item>Spread about 2 tablespoons of the mushroom mixture on one slice and cover with the other slice.</item>
        <item>You can now grill the Mushroom Sandwiches using a Panini Press or Sandwich Maker and serve warm.</item>
        <item>Serve the Grilled Mushroom Sandwich Recipe with Herbs for breakfast</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="south_veggie_dir">
        <item>Prepare the hummus by combining 1 can (drained and rinsed) black beans with the southwest black bean hummus package in a blender or food processor.</item>
        <item>Blend or pulse until smooth.</item>
        <item>Generously spread 4 large tortillas or pita bread with the hummus.</item>
        <item>Deseed and remove the stems from the peppers.</item>
        <item>Slice in thin slices.</item>
        <item>Top the tortillas evenly with the sliced peppers.</item>
        <item>Evenly disperse the remaining &#189; cup black beans and corn over the peppers.</item>
        <item>Slice the tomatoes and avocado.</item>
        <item>Add to the tortillas along with the cheese slices.</item>
        <item>Sprinkle salt and pepper over the tortillas and then add 2 tablespoons dressing to each tortilla.</item>
        <item>If desired add some fresh lime and coarsely chopped cilantro.</item>
        <item>Roll up and enjoy immediately.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="portabella_mushroom_dir">
        <item>Heat 1 tablespoon of olive oil in a large skillet over medium-high heat.</item>
        <item>Add mushrooms and cook 3 to 4 minutes, or until softened and browned.</item>
        <item>Add wine and increase heat to high.</item>
        <item>Cook until liquid has evaporated, about 2 to 3 minutes. Transfer to bowl.</item>
        <item>Preheat oven to 250 degrees.</item>
        <item>Carefully wipe skillet clean.</item>
        <item>Heat remaining tablespoon of olive oil over medium high heat.</item>
        <item>Add green pepper and onions; cook until softened, about 5 to 8 minutes.</item>
        <item>Reduce heat to low.</item>
        <item>Return mushrooms to skillet and stir to combine, then season to taste with salt and pepper.</item>
        <item>Top vegetable mixture with cheese slices.</item>
        <item>Once cheese has melted, remove from heat.</item>
        <item>Divide veggie mixture into sub rolls.</item>
        <item>Wrap each cheesesteak tightly with foil and place on a baking sheet.</item>
        <item>Bake for 15 minutes.</item>
        <item>Remove from oven and unwrap carefully.</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>